<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on (DD)uplicate! A Decentralized home for all GME DD</title>
    <link>/posts.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on (DD)uplicate! A Decentralized home for all GME DD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 19:13:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A House of Cards - Part 1 </title>
      <link>/posts/mvk5dv.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 17:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvk5dv.html</guid>
      <description>TL;DR- The DTC has been taken over by big money. They transitioned from a manual to a computerized ledger system in the 80s, and it played a significant role in the 1987 market crash. In 2003, several issuers with the DTC wanted to remove their securities from the DTC&amp;rsquo;s deposit account because the DTC&amp;rsquo;s participants were naked short selling their securities. Turns out, they were right. The DTC and it&amp;rsquo;s participants have created a market-sized naked short selling scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of Cards - Part 3 </title>
      <link>/posts/nlwqyv.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 01:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nlwqyv.html</guid>
      <description>Prerequisite DD:
 Citadel Has No Clothes (wb) The EVERYTHING Short (wb) The House of Cards – Part 1 (wb) The House of Cards - Part 2 (wb)  ____________________________________________________________________________________________________________
TL;DR- No freaking way I can do that.
_____________________________________________________________________________________________________________________
Continuing from HOC Part II&amp;hellip;
4. Slimy…
If you watched the AMA with Wes Christian (wb), he talks about the number of occurrences where the actual short interest is severely understated based on the data his firm obtained for legal proceedings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of Cards - Part 2 </title>
      <link>/posts/nlwaxv.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 01:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nlwaxv.html</guid>
      <description>Prerequisite DD:
  Citadel Has No Clothes (wb)
  The EVERYTHING Short (wb)
  The House of Cards – Part 1 (wb)
  ____________________________________________________________________________________________________________
TL;DR- No freaking way I can do that.
____________________________________________________________________________________________________________________
1. Pilot
I wasn’t looking into GameStop when all of this began. Most of my time was spent researching the pandemic’s impact on the economy. I’m talking about the economic steam engine that employs people and puts food on their tables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚨Blowing my diamond whistle- As a highly visible poster here, I want my apes to know. I have been offered money to post non-GME content in our stock subs. Beware everything you read until MOASS, no matter who is the OP!🚨 </title>
      <link>/posts/ms6yvq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 16:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ms6yvq.html</guid>
      <description>Labeling this DD because, aside from having to do with an offer to be paid to post DD, I actually performed due diligence on the offer (wb).
If you think those alarm posts yesterday about top posters here/YouTubers getting paid to distract apes during the MOASS was FUD, I&amp;rsquo;m here with proof it&amp;rsquo;s totally fucking true. (Details edited out for privacy. More on why below&amp;hellip;) I have now sent unedited proof of the company to mods just for public integrity so you all know I&amp;rsquo;m not making this up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THE MOTHER OF ALL WEDGES: AN ENDGAME DD. Technical and Fundamental Analysis with Warden. Where we are now, where we are headed. When might the MOASS begin? </title>
      <link>/posts/n5me5g.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 18:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n5me5g.html</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! It&amp;rsquo;s Warden. I&amp;rsquo;m taking a brief moment to write a chart analysis post because I feel that we are nearing a critical junction point. The volume today has been extremely low, currently sitting at around 1.7 million, and I feel that a lot of people are sensing that something big is coming. I&amp;rsquo;ve emptied the rest of my bank account into the dip today to buy more tickets to the moon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We&#39;re STILL Trading Sideways and Why We Haven&#39;t Launched </title>
      <link>/posts/mu9xed.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mu9xed.html</guid>
      <description>EDIT May 12, 2021: SR-OCC-2021-004 Is Scheduled to Finalize This Week (wb) ^(Also, I have been banned from Superstonk&amp;hellip;)
EDIT May 18, 2021: I have been unbanned; thanks for all the folks who reached out and thanks to the mods!
We&amp;rsquo;ve made it through an exciting weekend of suspense only to end up with yet another day of sideways trading. I&amp;rsquo;d like to examine why I think we have not yet launched based on the bits and pieces that we know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy shit. I was skeptical of all the high ceilings being thrown out until I put the pieces together. I honestly think GME is priceless, and the most valuable stock you will ever buy. Here&#39;s the full picture, as I understand it... </title>
      <link>/posts/mvcqpi.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 10:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvcqpi.html</guid>
      <description>First of all, I’d like to start off by stating this post is completely nonpartisan. GME is not a political debate, it’s a class war.
Okay, let me ask you guys this — how many of you knew that when the pandemic began, the FED pumped $3 trillion dollars into the markets? I watch the news in the background all day, every day, and I didn’t know at the time when the injections were happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The flurry of rules before the storm. DTC, ICC, OCC are prepared. GME might be hitting T&#43;35 and T&#43;21 crossover next week, pulling the house of cards down. </title>
      <link>/posts/ngru15.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 05:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ngru15.html</guid>
      <description>Preface ==========  I&amp;rsquo;m not a financial advisor - and I am not providing you financial advice! This is all my interpretation of what is going on.
Anyways, I wanted to ask&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;m hype. Are you pretty hype? I keep coming back because I love you guys, and I love the fact that there has been so much research freely accessible to teach millions of people all the nooks and crannies of the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$GME - The Mother of All Short Squeezes (MOASS) Thesis. Summarized and broken down in a way for all (or most) to understand. We are in the end-game everyone, and this rocket is taking off with or without you. If you want to understand that whole &#34;GME thing&#34; this is my best shot at explaining it </title>
      <link>/posts/nletnn.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 11:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nletnn.html</guid>
      <description>Edit (6/7/2021): Made some significant additions and refinements to the content here (had to cut a bunch due to character limit :(
 Thanks u/redchessqueen99 and the Mods for choosing to drop the coveted &amp;quot; Not-A-Cat Golden Bananya Award&amp;quot; award on this. Too bad the primary contributor on this was my financial advisor who is a cat (I just plagiarized him)
 Personal note Feel free to use the contents of this post however you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/u/dlauer&#39;s most recent post correcting blatant misinformation isn&#39;t getting any traction. He even urges people who have had &#34;high cost basis when transferring out of Robinhood to file a whistleblower complaint&#34; </title>
      <link>/posts/ni0elf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 19:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ni0elf.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4/20 “Share Recall” Explained- Why it’s important that shares must be recorded-Is this the Catalyst?🚀🚀🚀 If you’re still on Margin, CONTACT YOUR BROKERS </title>
      <link>/posts/mmt5rq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 14:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mmt5rq.html</guid>
      <description>April 9 update: This piece has been heavily edited from its original presentation. I&amp;rsquo;ve had plenty of shit talk about this post. I get it. Some of y&amp;rsquo;all think I&amp;rsquo;m fucking r*tarded for even posting this. But NOT ALL APES HAVE BEEN HERE SINCE JANUARY. I&amp;rsquo;m just trying to help in my limited capacity. And it seems to have helped thousands of apes get their affairs in order before liftoff, so I stand by this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MOASS Preparation Guide </title>
      <link>/posts/mm5qle.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 16:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mm5qle.html</guid>
      <description>Please read though this and possibly sticky this because I think it is very important that we all have an understanding on the game plan 🚀
Pre-liftoff Preparation https://preview.redd.it/pyg5a96r4sr61.jpg?width=1280&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=97c4b8bfe4b63214cee3c8e5aaed8d5519d4db10
 Brokers preparation - i think everyone should take the time to understand the nuances and rules that the broker applies on trading. Some brokers may have some sneaky fine prints. So you should make sure that nothing can get in the way of you and your tendies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things are shockingly similar to the February 24th and March 10th runup so far. Gamma squeeze indicators from the previous T&#43;21/T&#43;35 have returned. Their doom approaches. </title>
      <link>/posts/nqbera.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 02:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nqbera.html</guid>
      <description>Preface ==========  I am not a financial advisor, and I do not provide financial advice! Everything within this post is my opinion and observations. They should be taken with skepticism. So grab a crayon my friends! June has started off absolutely wild!
TL;DR: Hedgies are close to meeting their doom (wb). DOOOM.
Actual TL;DR: June 1st has kicked off with the DTC, ICC, OCC auction and wind-down plans officially being in place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The naked shorting scam in numbers: AI detection of 140M hidden FTDs, up to 400M naked shorts in married puts and massive dark pool activity by Shitadel and the shorts </title>
      <link>/posts/mvdgf5.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 11:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvdgf5.html</guid>
      <description>Edit: I made a new post describing how I trained the binary classifier (AI) used in this post (wb).
This could be it. This could be the whole scam.
TLDR: HODL. Simple as that. HODL and the shorts have no way to escape. They just writhe around in desperation as FTDs escalate, their options expire and New DTCC rulings approach. To support this belief I:
 Built an AI to detect Deep ITM calls used to create naked shares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRAFT: I have done my best to summarize the GME MOASS Thesis in a way that hopefully appeals to individuals outside of this community. I was thinking about reposting before opening bell tomorrow with updates depending on feedback I get tonight. Intention is for it to be a starting point prior to DD </title>
      <link>/posts/njln8o.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/njln8o.html</guid>
      <description>Updated version - https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/nletnn/gme_the_mother_of_all_short_squeezes_moass_thesis/?utm_medium=android_app&amp;amp;utm_source=share
Intro: This post will give a relatively simplistic breakdown of the current situation and landscape of GameStop Stock, or GME (its name on the New York Stock Exchange NYSE), and to summarize the theory that it will soon reach astronomical levels during a market event known as a Short Squeeze. For specifically, this theory is the MOASS (Mother of All Short Squeezes) Thesis.
The core intention of the post is to summarize the MOASS Thesis for investors who are not fully up to speed on it, as well as those who are newer to the stock market in general, and are interested in investing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hank&#39;s Big Bang: Quant Apes Glitch the Simulation </title>
      <link>/posts/nu9qq9.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nu9qq9.html</guid>
      <description>************ I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice ************
Edit: Credit for the correlation tables to u/phalanxhydra
Edit 2: I am retarded. It&amp;rsquo;s u/Ivorypetal.
Introduction Apes, because of the sheer amount of information in this post and because I wanted to get it to you at the beginning of this week because of earnings and the meeting, this post will not have the usual funny intro and memes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hank&#39;s Definitive GME Theory of Everything </title>
      <link>/posts/n66tzh.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 13:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n66tzh.html</guid>
      <description>************ I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice ************
Introduction (DD starts below) Apes, did you know that there are usually about 80 confirmed cases of deadly shark attacks per year. You know what nobody ever talks about though? The fact that sharks have TWO, count it TWO, FUCKING PENSIS. I am not making that up. Imagine what I could do with two penises. I&amp;rsquo;d have twice the total dick length.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actually useful info you might have missed, 23/04/21 </title>
      <link>/posts/mwuszf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 13:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mwuszf.html</guid>
      <description>The shitshow this morning is arguably the result of forum sliding, so let&amp;rsquo;s counter that by collating some of the better stuff until the mods can clean up the front page. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I found buried that is probably of interest.
 u/broccaaa has posted a follow-up to his earlier post about trying to detect hidden FTDs with machine learning. It outlines the method behind his data labeling and the AI architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glacier Capital Exists - And It&#39;s Much Spicer Than You Thought </title>
      <link>/posts/nf2q78.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 05:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nf2q78.html</guid>
      <description>(Skip to !!!!!!! - This was the initial part of my investigation. Skip to that bit. Promise.)
In the linked in profile, they are advertising for one position in China with email domains for glacierchina.com (wb)
Running the advertisement through Google Translate, we can see that they have a public WeChat account: GlacierCap.
Throughout the rest of the job post, they refer themselves to Gengxin Capital.
 Introduction:
 Founded in September 2018, Gengxin Capital is an enabling boutique investment bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve estimated the current SI% based on the SI Report Cycle and Deep ITM CALL purchases. </title>
      <link>/posts/nc1lny.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 05:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nc1lny.html</guid>
      <description>Preface ==========  Not a financial advisor. Yada yada. If you actually listen to me you might want to get your brain checked for crayons.
Probably no need for any more DDs from me after this one - its a cumulation of my thoughts over the past few months. People were interested in an SI% estimate so I thought, hell yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s interesting shit. Why not?
On a side note, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned pretty much everything I have about the stock market from Peppa Pig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walkin&#39; like a duck. Talkin&#39; like a duck </title>
      <link>/posts/ml48ov.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ml48ov.html</guid>
      <description>TL;DR - I have prepared a case which strongly indicates that Citadel Securities, along with it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;affiliates&amp;rdquo; are committing securities fraud. On March 26th 2021, FINRA released a new citation against Citadel Securities for nearly 2 years worth of securities violations. The only reason Citadel HASN&amp;rsquo;T been busted for fraud is because they hide behind the veil of &amp;lsquo;unintentional&amp;rsquo; behavior. However, this post illustrates how Citadel&amp;rsquo;s actions flag ALL 3 corners of the fraud triangle- pressure, motivation, and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Shorts Must Cover. They&#39;re Entering The Danger Zone. The SI Report Loop Consistently Brings Us Ever Closer To The Squeeze. </title>
      <link>/posts/n792mf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 21:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n792mf.html</guid>
      <description>Preface ==========  This is your daily hit of hopium. In this case maybe a full rip of it since I see many people discouraged about 002 - but there is no need to worry. I want to show you that apes are winning and shorts are losing. You hold, you win. (But please note I am not a financial advisor. I don&amp;rsquo;t want you guys bitching at me if you YOLO it on deep OTM options expiring within 24 hours).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shitadel HQ oddly busy right now on a weekend night. Wonder who&#39;s working overtime shredding papers? </title>
      <link>/posts/mt4j8w.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 02:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mt4j8w.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tombstone Tweet Confirms Reverse Merger? Reposted Reverse Merger DD </title>
      <link>/posts/nnmb4c.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 12:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nnmb4c.html</guid>
      <description>​
&amp;ldquo;A tombstone is a written advertisement that gives investors basic details about an upcoming public offering.&amp;rdquo;
EDIT #1 THANKS FOR ALL THE UPVOTES! I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect this to blowup as I was just reposting it in light of the tweet. This is my theory based on facts. Also a great timeline of rc involvement with GME. Gamestop future is very bright in the near term and future. Not financial advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you STILL dont understand why today we went red again after we were big green yesterday and WHY you should get a hold of yourself and stop fucking caring. </title>
      <link>/posts/mrgj8c.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mrgj8c.html</guid>
      <description>I swear to god this place is like a daycare sometimes. You all go wild if we go green, and you get despressed and FUDdy if we go red. You STILL don&amp;rsquo;t understand why the price doesn&amp;rsquo;t fucking matter&amp;hellip;.
I made this post in the daily and it was highly upvoted, and I was asked to post it like this too.
Here goes.
Guys I can&amp;rsquo;t believe some of you still dont understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackrock just rang the alarm on CNBC regarding the impending market crash!! </title>
      <link>/posts/mu4ido.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 16:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mu4ido.html</guid>
      <description>Black rock on CNBC ringing the alarm- too much liquidity in the market. “FEELS FROTHY.”
Link below, just watched live.CNBC usually uploads these vids to YouTube later.
Edit: From google- “Too much liquidity risks the creation of asset bubbles, like in housing before the financial crisis and farm land afterwards, and distorts financial markets. Throughout the world, ongoing central bank liquidity has bolstered financial assets rather than goods and services that produce growth in the real economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This drop is synthetic and I think we might be holding for longer than we expect before the tendieman comes. Be prepared for that and don&#39;t get fatigued. </title>
      <link>/posts/mwbk4y.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 18:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mwbk4y.html</guid>
      <description>I have been taking some looks at the Level 2 information and it seems that when &amp;ldquo;they&amp;rdquo; want to drop the price, &amp;ldquo;they&amp;rdquo; use smaller lots of bids and asks - today was lots of 11 - 11 shares were being traded back and forth the entire time we saw a drop in the price down by $10. Other apes have noticed this before. See image 1.
I then noticed they stopped trading in these lots, see image 2 below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/5/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. The great migration edition. </title>
      <link>/posts/mkkj0p.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 13:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mkkj0p.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 172, 176.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.5, 218, 226, 230, 234, 243, 250, 253, 256.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚀 Time to expose the shell game. FTDs can be &#34;reset&#34; through borrowing from ETFs. Read the Truth. </title>
      <link>/posts/mvvmvp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 02:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvvmvp.html</guid>
      <description>🚀 Time to expose the shell game. The Shell Game
FTDs are not “reset”. FTDs on ETFs help show the short positions on the underlying securities. Edit: Each Shell Game post is intended to be read sequentially. You&amp;rsquo;ve been misinformed on FTDs. You&amp;rsquo;ll feel great after you go through this journey with me.
 Shell Game II (wb) Shell Game III (wb)  Many talented DD writers have theorized that FTDs are being reset using deep ITM call options and although it appears to be a credible theory that no doubt applies to many stocks, the singular attention it receives may have clouded our vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Got What You Quant - 6/2/21 Trading Analysis and a Deeper Dive Into Today&#39;s Tape </title>
      <link>/posts/nqzo1o.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 23:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nqzo1o.html</guid>
      <description>HOLY MOLY! GME has highest close since 1/29! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen yesterday&amp;rsquo;s POST (wb), I recommend taking a look before getting into today&amp;rsquo;s action, because BIG THINGS ARE HAPPENING! Congrats to the 💎🖐🦍 that like movies, as without you, GME wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be on the brink of launch. Prepare yourself, it&amp;rsquo;s time for the tea. This is not financial advice, my 🧠 is smooth.
​
Up until 5/27, GME price movements were strongly correlated to AMC, making the year to date R^(2) value between the two 76%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The end has begun. (IMPORTANT INFO INSIDE) </title>
      <link>/posts/n59n8x.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 06:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n59n8x.html</guid>
      <description>https://www.dtcc.com/-/media/Files/pdf/2021/5/4/B15129-21.pdf (wb)
DTCC is imposing a 100% haircut for MBS bonds &amp;ldquo;Not Rated or Rated below Aa2/AA&amp;rdquo;
What does this mean?
What is a &amp;ldquo;haircut&amp;rdquo;?
Source: http://www.columbia.edu/~td2332/Paper_Repo.pdf (wb)
&amp;quot; The recent financial crisis centered on the sale and repurchase (“repo”) market, a very large short-term collateralized debt market. Repo transactions often involve overcollateralization. The extent of overcollateralization is known as a “haircut.” Why do haircuts exist? And what determine the size of the haircut?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The March to Zero Liquidity: Volume or Bust </title>
      <link>/posts/n3ehw0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 19:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n3ehw0.html</guid>
      <description>Edit 1: Requested TL;DR - Remember that scene in Independence Day where the great Will Smith during a dogfight takes the baddie alien super low and into the canyon before they both crash? Or when we lost the indomitable Jamie Foxx in Stealth? Well, the lower you go the higher the probability there is for fatal error. GME volume has been suppressed to a point where any slight mistake by Citadel or added buy pressure will make price go BOOM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SR-DTC-2021-004, The DTCC and J.P Morgan. They&#39;re getting ready for defaults and bankruptcies, they&#39;ve just opened THREE additional netting accounts. </title>
      <link>/posts/mur8bz.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 14:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mur8bz.html</guid>
      <description>Edits at the bottom
​
I know what you&amp;rsquo;re thinking. What the hell is a netting account and why does this matter?
​
WELL.
​
My wonderful apes let me feed you with some information. As always, I know nothing and may be putting 2+2 together to make banana. Please critique and help me fill in the gaps, my knowledge on this started approximately 10 minutes ago.
​
The background ​</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CITADEL, MARGIN CALL, 1M MISSING SHARES &amp; THE TRADING HALT </title>
      <link>/posts/n5yl8r.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 03:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n5yl8r.html</guid>
      <description>^(Sit the fuck down before you read this.)
MY THEORY: u/Leenixus was almost certainly correct in Thinking that &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rdquo; got margin called today (wb).
In After Hours 1M shares seemed to &amp;ldquo;disappear&amp;rdquo; from EOD Volume before &amp;ldquo;reappearing&amp;rdquo; in the EOD Volume later before AH close. I BELIEVE this is because Citadel got margin called @ 1127 today and therefor those 1M shares traded had to be re-routed or re-done or what have you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Major Deep ITM CALL Option Dates. A Massive Net Capital BOMB Might Explode This Week. </title>
      <link>/posts/n4h832.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 05:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n4h832.html</guid>
      <description>Update =========  Edit: Ah here we are after cinco de buyo. No big price move was made. That&amp;rsquo;s some good shit if you ask me. The prediction was that we&amp;rsquo;d see a price surge again if they delayed FTDs once more. The fact that it didn&amp;rsquo;t happen today - no Deep ITM CALLs or PUTs occurred today - is reason to believe this is almost over. If Net Capital theory is correct, there&amp;rsquo;s two possibilities here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another GME DD dump from Hank </title>
      <link>/posts/nnsfs6.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 17:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nnsfs6.html</guid>
      <description>************ I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice ************
Apes, I&amp;rsquo;ve recently gotten into comedy and wanted to test out some of my jokes on you:
Why did the chicken cross the road? Because my wife is fucking the mailman.
What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between GME and my wife? GME doesn&amp;rsquo;t have four boyfriends.
How many HFs does it take to screw in a lightbulb? Seriously guys my wife is a cheating whore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GameStop can now pay dividends, they do not need to wait until April 30th! </title>
      <link>/posts/mqh3ep.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 02:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mqh3ep.html</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: GameStop is allowed to pay dividends as soon as it deposits the funds for their note buyback - which it can do at any point after the filing of the redemption notice and before the redemption date. If they have already deposited the funds, they can declare a dividend.
​
I have been looking at the indenture filing related to the 2023 debts GameStop announced they are paying out on the 30th of this month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS THEORY - The FINAL Connection </title>
      <link>/posts/mseyai.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 23:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mseyai.html</guid>
      <description>The final picture is starting to come together. The ties of the former CFTC (who now works for citadel) &amp;amp; SEC chairmen to the industry appear to be pointing to fraudulent activity in efforts to prolong the necessity of SOFR being implemented. SOFR the last time it was attempted to transitioned into (in 2019) almost IMPLODED the market due to many realizing that banks and others could not handle a higher interest rate (based off the DAILY TRESURY YIELD RATE (wb)) versus the fabricated one that banks provide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEC Filing: Merger with brokarage, detailing lawssuit, mentions 30 brokerages engaging in coordinated conspiracy </title>
      <link>/posts/mq4gfi.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 15:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mq4gfi.html</guid>
      <description>SEC Filing for Northen Star and Apex merger link: S-4 (sec.gov) (wb)
Addendum— these lawsuits are mentioned in an upcoming merger- lawsuits related to the debacle fall out from GME in January - the reason I think it’s a positive thing is the merging brokerage must disclose and they state an increase of awareness of market manipulation and this makes them more liable and also more apt to regard Sec laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules still have to go through the approval process with the DTCC and the SEC... all 006 removes is the 10 days it takes for a rule to get implemented after it’s been through that approval process... Misinformation is spreading like wildfire. This will NOT expedite the approval process with the SEC. </title>
      <link>/posts/n7qem3.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 14:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n7qem3.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motley Fool is a hedgefund with a newspaper bahahaha </title>
      <link>/posts/ms7s31.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 17:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ms7s31.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve been scraping data used by hedge funds for over a year now to make it freely available to everyone. I think I might start doing regular data reports on $GME on here if there&#39;s interest, let me know if you have any feedback on the report below. </title>
      <link>/posts/mlevq3.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 15:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mlevq3.html</guid>
      <description>Hey guys pdwp90 here, founder of Quiver Quantitative (wb) for those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know me by Reddit tag.
This report is primarily comprised of &amp;ldquo;alternative data&amp;rdquo; which can be loosely thought of as data that comes from outside of traditional sources like earnings reports. The reason this type of data gets me so jacked is because it&amp;rsquo;s data that retail investors (you guys) often have an edge over Wall Street in interpreting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a followup to the HoC DD- the &#34;everything&#34; in Everything Short. I present, RAGNAROK </title>
      <link>/posts/no14pt.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 01:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/no14pt.html</guid>
      <description>Atobitt made some great DD. House of Cards 1-3. Everything Short. Classics. However, part 2 and 3 of HoC felt incomplete. No offense to the man, no offense to the data. I think it is spot on, i think we all know what to do. HODL.
But, I am here to add this, somewhat controversial, somewhat illuminating piece of information. I hesitate to post this because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to insinuate there are other plays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KEN GRIFFIN EXPOSED </title>
      <link>/posts/mou8ww.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 16:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mou8ww.html</guid>
      <description>An overview of the deplorable Mr. Ken Griffin
​
My fellow apes,
I believe it was Sun Tzu who said &amp;ldquo;If you know the enemy and know yourself, you need not fear the result of a hundred battles.&amp;rdquo; That is what we face every trading day, as the saga of GME continues.
I am keen to inform you further about the antagonist of this story (though I&amp;rsquo;m sure as a likely narcissistic psychopath he doesn&amp;rsquo;t see it that way).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SRO Filings </title>
      <link>/posts/n9326x.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 12:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n9326x.html</guid>
      <description>Recently there has been a screenshot of a NYSE SRO filing being circulated purporting to show that NYSE is &amp;ldquo;suspending a ton of dark pool groups.&amp;rdquo; Or that NYSE is appealing an SEC ruling or something like that.
So to start, NYSE has nothing to do with dark pools. NYSE is a lit exchange regulated under the Exchange Act, while dark pools are &amp;ldquo;Alternative Trading Systems&amp;rdquo; regulated completely differently (a combination of the SEC and FINRA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE -- Go / No-Go For Launch - The checklist keeping GME on the launchpad. </title>
      <link>/posts/nhh0f1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 01:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nhh0f1.html</guid>
      <description>TL;DR:
DTCC / OCC / ICC etc. &amp;amp; Wall St want key things in place before GME unwinds, and we&amp;rsquo;re now looking at a list that&amp;rsquo;s been mostly checked off. This rocket is just about cleared for launch.
Last updated: 2021-05-28 | Original post from 2021-04-22 (wb)
Go / No-Go For Launch Opinion - Status: Hold ❌
We&amp;rsquo;re on a scheduled hold. Preliminary system checks are good enough to launch, and now we are being held for atmospheric conditions to be just right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I am Ecstatic GME is Taking a Dump, and the Possible Correlation with AMC and Crypto </title>
      <link>/posts/nn370o.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 17:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nn370o.html</guid>
      <description>Apes, lend me your ears.
I am pumped that GME took a fat dive from $268.80 down to below $235.00 as of this post. Why? Because it means we&amp;rsquo;ve figured out the modus operandi of the shorts, and HFs are fuk.
TL;DR HODL, because GME is going to the moon. 🚀
T+35/T+21 Cycles This is real, and the juiciest part of this post. As I noted in my Cyclical Patterns in Failure-To-Deliver (FTD) and Short Interest Reporting (wb), written upon the DD of those before me, the T+35/T+21 cycles are consistent, empirical, measurable, and now, predictable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AndrewMoMoney Used My DD In A Live Stream Ft. Shill Sniffing Dog And Deleted My Comment, So I Analyzed His Channel </title>
      <link>/posts/myryiv.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 07:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/myryiv.html</guid>
      <description>Edit: I can&amp;rsquo;t believe&amp;hellip;I spent all weekend writing this&amp;hellip; only for you guys&amp;hellip; to react&amp;hellip; the way I expected you to! How exciting!! pulls up soap box So alright y&amp;rsquo;all, now that you&amp;rsquo;re all here, let me make a brief comment before I go to bed and I&amp;rsquo;ll see you later if the mods allow it. I see red flag, I investigate, I report my findings. You can agree, disagree, or anything in between and I will not lose a wink of sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRICE ACTION IS SHOCKINGLY similar to NOT ONLY the 2/24-3/10 runup, but also to the JANUARY run from $20 - $480. T&#43;35 / T&#43;21 elaboration. </title>
      <link>/posts/nrud2r.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 02:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nrud2r.html</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll start with the usual: I am not a financial advisor. I do not provide financial advice! Everything following this is opinion/observation. Much of my knowledge of the markets has been acquired through reading countless hours of DD posted by others in this sub.
I&amp;rsquo;m not one to buy into the echoed phrases of this sub&amp;hellip; but I am in fact JaCKeD tO tHe TiTs!
OBLIGATORY - BuY &amp;amp; HoDl!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 22, February 19, March 5, April 16. The only options available in early 2020 and why tomorrow might be ignition. </title>
      <link>/posts/mv740t.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mv740t.html</guid>
      <description>Edit: RIParoni. I&amp;rsquo;m currently rethinking this. You will notice that bursts almost always happen on wednesdays. I still believe there is a pattern and we should be able to pin down a date for another gamma burst.
I know, I know. Dates. Whatever. Stay with me for a moment please. (wb) I have high confidence that we are going to see a repeat of February 24th, and the MOASS will start tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OBV and Beta definitively show that the price is heavily suppressed and that GME is the ultimate hedge against market volatility </title>
      <link>/posts/n9mkoj.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 02:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n9mkoj.html</guid>
      <description>Hey there, dildos and dildettes. I normally keep my DD to myself and my friends, but if I can convince my cautious anchor to reality that GME is going to the moon, maybe I can help you do the same.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have someone keeping you grounded and real, you should. Fiery passion only beats cold hard facts in Julie Garwood novels and succubus hentai.
OBV
OBV = On Balance Volume and typically it follows the price movement closer than Citadel interns follow this sub for the latest image of Kenneth as an alien covered in nipples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Over 30% of GME bananas are missing from Bloomberg Terminal. Over 69% of GME is trading off exchanges or in an unreported Dark Pool? It&#39;s National Banana Day - Do you know where your GME bananas are? </title>
      <link>/posts/mvfs0c.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 13:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvfs0c.html</guid>
      <description>So yesterday I posted about FINRA ADF showing up as the primary exchange for GME trades over the past 6 trading days (and likely much longer). The thing is, FINRA ADF is not currently in operation&amp;hellip;
https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/muzj4o/finra_webmaster_no_brokerdealers_currently_using/ (wb)
u/koreanjc had a great post about this a little over a week ago FADF - A Dark Pool (wb)
While looking into this, I realized that the GME Bloomberg Terminal data is missing between 31.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Koreans have bought around 1.5million shares of Gamestop since April </title>
      <link>/posts/n6o6co.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 02:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n6o6co.html</guid>
      <description>A family member just sent me an article about Gamestop, and other &amp;ldquo;meme&amp;rdquo; stocks. Basically the article tries to spread FUD about investing in &amp;ldquo;meme&amp;rdquo; stocks, with Gamestop being the top of the list.
I read the article, but they provide no convincing arguments with regards to their title. What&amp;rsquo;s interesting though, is that they have a chart showing how much money went into buying Gamestop from Korea. The figure is shown below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hank Returns.... WITH SOME FTD CYCLE DD </title>
      <link>/posts/myxei0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/myxei0.html</guid>
      <description>I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice
A post-shack salute from Uncle Hank Oh boy have I missed you, my Apes. I come to you as a primate reborn. I haven&amp;rsquo;t shaved, showered, or talked to my dad in four months&amp;hellip; yeah this 3-day sabbatical really took a toll on me. After taking my sabbatical where I only drank WD40 and coconut oil, only ate pringles, fig newtons, gushers, and Cheetos, only listened to Fifth Harmony, Megan Thee Stallion, and Linkin Park, only used the bathroom ONCE per day, and only called my wife&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend for 45 minutes per day (thank god that&amp;rsquo;s over, I need my 8 hours), I come to you as an enlightened primate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infinity War: The Final Exit DD Compilation </title>
      <link>/posts/nogxnr.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 18:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nogxnr.html</guid>
      <description>Hello Superstonk!
I am just compiling this for those of you that might be interested in the more juicy non-TA parts of my weekly DD&amp;rsquo;s. Since a lot of this was written over several weeks, I wanted to get it all into one place for ease of reference. Any additional exit strategies or information will be added to this post in the future.
For those of you that prefer the Video DD&amp;rsquo;s they can still be found over on my YouTube (wb).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THEORY: Robinhood is buying counterfeit shares from Citadel at inflated prices to move capital towards the mothership, trying to prevent the margin call </title>
      <link>/posts/nh2lzv.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 15:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nh2lzv.html</guid>
      <description>LAST EDIT; THIS THEORY HAS BEEN PARTIALLY DISPROVED BY DLAURER; https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/nhtt04/cost_basis_and_trade_price_issues/ (wb)
THE ONLY RIGHT COURSE OF ACTION IS FILING A WHISTLEBLOWER COMPLAINT WITH THE SEC IF THESE PRICES HAPPENED TO YOU; https://www.sec.gov/whistleblower (wb)
​
Dear Apes,
​
As many of you know, there are multiple reports coming in from various ex-Robinhood apes showing at which prices their shares had to be bought and found in order to finish their transfer to other brokers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[UPDATED] DD: I did the math, there is literally NO DOUBT that we own &gt;100% of the remaining float. [including updated remaining float from GME&#39;s proxy statement] 🚀🚀🚀 </title>
      <link>/posts/mxrdcb.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 19:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mxrdcb.html</guid>
      <description>(clears throat) &amp;ldquo;ehem !&amp;quot;
First of all: Many thanks for all the great feedback you freaking apes gave me on my initial DD (wb) on r/GME. As some time (around 1 month) has passed and we have some new apes and apettes on board and some new information around my initial assumptions has been updated and revealed, I have decided to work on an updated version of my initial DD. So let&amp;rsquo;s start right away, main changes are as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check out DFV&#39;s DD on Gamestop if you haven&#39;t already, it&#39;s now more relevant than ever. and several predictions in this clip already came true🔥🔥🔥 </title>
      <link>/posts/myi25g.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 21:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/myi25g.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This week might be it; the brakes are possibly ready to come off (SR-OCC-2021-004 and MORE) </title>
      <link>/posts/nfagu1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 13:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nfagu1.html</guid>
      <description>EDIT: May 20 - So good, Tim Fries at the Tokenist shamelessly lifted this DD (wb) 🤣
​
I emphasize &amp;ldquo;might&amp;rdquo;. See below and judge for yourself.
TL;DR:
 On Monday, May 17th, OCC posted an increase to their Clearing Fund of $588,378,155 (wb). This information was found by u/aSphericalCow. In case it isn&amp;rsquo;t clear, OCC is saying that all members must contribute proportionally to add $588m to the common Clearing Fund by Wednesday, May 19 (tomorrow).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SR-NSCC-2021-801 CONFIRMATION (MAY THE 4TH BE WITH YOU) </title>
      <link>/posts/n49zl5.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 23:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n49zl5.html</guid>
      <description>Congratulations to everyone wo had bought the dip in the disccounts of today. Sorry for my english  Hi again, I published this post yesterday The SR-NSCC-2021-801 CAN be approved AUTOMATICALLY this week. (MAY THE 4TH BE WITH YOU). (wb)
I saw some people saying that this rules had changes. But anyone could confirm that if these changes can change the rule of 60 days. So I decided to send an email to the people who propose the law changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>801 and NSCC-002 </title>
      <link>/posts/n5idj9.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n5idj9.html</guid>
      <description>CREDIT TO u/FATJUUL FOR STRUCTURE AND INFO
MAY 7th Edit: They have postponed the ruling until June 21st, please see my followup post: https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/n6zgng/nsc002_delayed_for_longer_period_of_comment_and/
I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen as much talk about this, yet it is the biggest news to come and IT IS the endgame catalyst.
NSCC-801 Passed with no objections yesterday. For this rule to enter effect it needs to piggyback on NSCC-002, which if no objections are made again, will be passed this Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GME Masters&#39; Guide: A DD Campaign for Apes Levels 1-20 (The GME Story in 100 DDs) </title>
      <link>/posts/njwv6n.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/njwv6n.html</guid>
      <description>Hi all, Blanderson here, back this time with all the DD you wanted in a story you didn&amp;rsquo;t ask for.
Here are 100+ DDs that have shaped the GME saga.
This is the story of you, Apes, and the DD writers who have held us together and made us proud. As always, I hope you will enjoy.
I polled the Daily Chat about the name of this post and wanted to shout out some of the top alternatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New OCC filing seeks to amend the process for liquidating positions for suspended options clearing members. (Citadel is an options clearing member) SR-OCC-2021-004 </title>
      <link>/posts/mkpgss.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 17:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mkpgss.html</guid>
      <description>Some people are getting a little confused. These &amp;ldquo;auctions&amp;rdquo; are not for GME stonk or any other stock for that matter. These are for open options contracts in other companies that have yet to expire and will need to be sold to cover short positions. The OCC handles all options transactions while the NSCC handles securities (stocks) transactions.
This rule is set to drop tomorrow (April 6, 2021) on the federal register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A GameStop customer confirming an Xbox controller was delivered with same day delivery today. A sign of Chewy-level customer service being demonstrated? </title>
      <link>/posts/mt056n.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mt056n.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JP Morgan spoofed their earnings to get investors interested, then sells $13 Billion in bonds to keep them afloat during the MOASS. </title>
      <link>/posts/mrrwz5.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mrrwz5.html</guid>
      <description>​
https://preview.redd.it/invn7a47rft61.png?width=1354&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ac92dab535457b17e24eae84f1e1b5ef550099ff
I would just like to firstly say this is just theory, don&amp;rsquo;t listen to anything I say as i&amp;rsquo;m a smooth brain.
So if you didn&amp;rsquo;t see yesterday JP Morgan&amp;rsquo;s net profit soars 5-fold to $14.3 billion (wb). I find this to be a little unlikely to be honest. We are on the the biggest bull run this market has ever seen, and the money printers keep on running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Repos Showing Possible Evidence of Forced Liquidations </title>
      <link>/posts/nlxom6.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 02:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nlxom6.html</guid>
      <description>Pre-DD Message: Hello you beautiful apes! Before I get into this DD I just wanted to say that I am so proud of everyone for holding against these wall street crooks. We&amp;rsquo;re finally starting to see some change happen and more and more people are starting to catch on to how fucked of a position the hedgies are really in right now, and it genuinely makes me happy that we&amp;rsquo;ve come from just some stupid retail investors looking for a quick buck to an educated mastermind of apes who scour the sub for DD and knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>04/10/2021 - THE FUD NEWS ON MELVIN – STOP BELIEVING MSM WHEN ITS CONFIRMATION BIAS – DAILY FUD REPORT </title>
      <link>/posts/mo038k.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 07:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mo038k.html</guid>
      <description>Edit - 04/11/2021 - The Fake Squeeze theory - Daily FUD Report (wb) - I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to go in depth a little more on the fake squeeze theory in &amp;lsquo;tomorrows&amp;rsquo; FUD report.
​
EDIT (AGAIN) - For everyone saying that &amp;lsquo;it might just be true&amp;rsquo;, think about the most glaringly obvious problem.
They used Bloomberg and Reuters previously to push the &amp;lsquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve covered&amp;rsquo; narrative (via anonymous source) back in February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hank visits GME&#39;s Bermuda Triangle (gone sexual) </title>
      <link>/posts/n9vyr4.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 12:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n9vyr4.html</guid>
      <description>I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice
Edit: forgot to mention that the exact same thing seems to be happening with AMC, which further makes me believe that this is orchestrated!
Introduction Apes, I&amp;rsquo;ve relapsed. Yup, I did it. I stayed away from it for so long, but I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t kick the urge. Yes, I am doing another technical analysis on GME. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, I&amp;rsquo;m an addict.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PROOF of Artificial Price Movement: Spreadsheets with Statistics to Soothe the Soul </title>
      <link>/posts/n0a0hf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 08:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n0a0hf.html</guid>
      <description>Edit/Update: Thank you for the love and awards!!! I have posted a question about this to Dr. Timbrath’s AMA, here (wb), if anyone else is interested on her opinion of this.
Apes, our primate community has gone through a lot in the last 4 months. We’ve been called names, lied to, and manipulated through the same PsyOps techniques typically used on extremist groups. Throughout everything you beautiful people have remained stubborn and hyper-rational while never losing your love of crayons, and I have never been more proud to be an ape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The mandatory DTCC Common Stock Reallocation for DTCC participants and the return to HOURLY MBSD Intraday Mark-to-Market Charges will certainly hurt those short on GME. Remember though, NO DATES! </title>
      <link>/posts/n3m0qu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 02:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n3m0qu.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is SR-DTC-2021-005? THE UPDATE !! </title>
      <link>/posts/ngwhzu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 10:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ngwhzu.html</guid>
      <description>Hello Fellow Apes,
I am writing this post to let Apes know that I was able to follow-up through the SEC and the DTCC on SR-DTC-2021-005 and to the follow-up on work in my initial post here (wb), and providing you now with the status update I received.
I would also like to report that the SEC and the DTCC once again were very gracious and timely in their responses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shorts must cover </title>
      <link>/posts/mw1txe.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 10:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mw1txe.html</guid>
      <description>So, from one smoothbrain to another. Apparently that u/Atobitt (wb) thing with his GOD TIER DD &amp;ldquo;House of cards&amp;rdquo; made some folks very insecure. Fuck, even I was completely devastated yesterday when I read it. With huge efforts I got my first wrinkle after thinking this through. Since I am not a genius, but I still want to pollute the internet like any other moron with my uninformed, unasked opinion, here is what I came up with, in hopes of helping some of you to make the right decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hank returns from the dead and takes a dump </title>
      <link>/posts/nhs1wy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 13:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nhs1wy.html</guid>
      <description>*********** I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice ************
Good morning apes, I&amp;rsquo;m back.
Boy is it good to be back, apes. I&amp;rsquo;ve missed you all. I&amp;rsquo;ve been gone for a while but have not left the cause. I&amp;rsquo;ve been lurking in the shadows, jacking off to DD, and huffing WD40. When I was just a child (a boy in Bulgaria), my father said he was going to the store to get cigarettes&amp;hellip; I think he&amp;rsquo;s still there, must&amp;rsquo;ve been a long line for those Marlboros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LATEST Failure-To-Deliver data from ALL 72 ETFs CONTAINING GME! ETFs containing 99% of all FTDs! </title>
      <link>/posts/ms6mvf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 16:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ms6mvf.html</guid>
      <description>Hello, this morning u/rensole did a request in his synopsis to analyse all the Failure-To-Delivers contained in the ETFs. So I made a Python script where I get all the latest FTD data from the 72 ETFs including GME. I will from now on post the FTD data for you apes. I hope you guys enjoy it! 🦍🦍
EDIT: Thank you so much for all your kind words! Love you all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, those patterns y&#39;all keep posting are real! The similarity in meme stock price movement is statistically significant and differs significantly from a control group of boomer stocks (answer to u/HomeDepotHank69). </title>
      <link>/posts/ns8dhk.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 15:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ns8dhk.html</guid>
      <description>So, this post is in response to u/HomeDepotHank69 ‘s request for DD into correlation between stock price movements.
TL/DR:
 Two different scientific methods showing that there is similarity and correlation between certain meme stocks and that this increased since Jan. A machine learning method asked to put stonk data into clusters based on their patterns over the last half year put the meme stonks GME, AMC, KOSS, and others together regardless of which bit of price data you choose to look at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚨EUROPOOR! 👀 Here is CARL HAGBERG&#39;s advice on HOW TO EXERCISE YOUR RIGHTS TO VOTE! Please do NOT capitulate. Do NOT acquiesce! YOU, Europoor, have a RIGHT. YOU have a VOICE. Follow Carl&#39;s ADVICE and heed Carl&#39;s words: &#34;VOTES HAVE VALUE!&#34; 🙏 Profit to the People. Power to the Players. 💎✊ </title>
      <link>/posts/nc8d2u.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 13:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nc8d2u.html</guid>
      <description>Hi Stonk, I will be happy to respond to your request below;
​
 &amp;hellip; for our Euro ape friends, many are still hitting resistance from their brokers on voting - can you provide maybe 5 bullet point steps they can do to maximize their voice and rights? Something I can post that really drives home the concrete measures they can take?
 ​
First. I want to make clear to the Euro apes that Europe is way ahead of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME Token Info </title>
      <link>/posts/nl0lk1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 21:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nl0lk1.html</guid>
      <description>I thought I&amp;rsquo;d summarize some information about the juicy morsel of information that was just discovered. I will try to keep it to information rather than opinion.
As has been rapidly circulating online, https://nft.gamestop.com/ (wb) was discovered. This site is real and official. You cannot fake a subdomain.
It has a curious little thing of numbers and letters near the bottom
Those who aren&amp;rsquo;t in crypto might not know that this is a an ERC (etherium) address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GME Wargame: A New Theory of Everything (My Final DD) 💗🦍🐒🚀🚀🚀 </title>
      <link>/posts/mvov2f.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvov2f.html</guid>
      <description>Nothing in my post should be assumed to accuse anyone of anything.
This is my theory of everything. My Charlie Day-DD. This is, I think, the blueprint for getting us through these last few agonizing days. Sorry, it&amp;rsquo;s walls of text, but I think you&amp;rsquo;ll enjoy reading it.
This will be the only meme.
This is in all likelihood my final statement on the matter until new information comes to light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where in the world is SR-DTC-2021-005. We were told over 1 month ago it was taken down for formatting and would be replaced in no more than 2 weeks. Let&#39;s talk about it. </title>
      <link>/posts/ncnz1l.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ncnz1l.html</guid>
      <description>Where in the world is Carmen San Diego SR-DTC-2021-005 otherwise known as &amp;ldquo;stop counting your shares twice&amp;rdquo; rule. We have passed record number of rules in the past month, and yet we have still not seen my (now second favorite to SR-ICC-2021-007 (wb)) rule come back in any form. It&amp;rsquo;s gone, vamos, does not exist on the internet. What the fucking fuck**?**
The contents cannot be found on the federal register: Federal register with search applied (wb)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Just a Pyramid Scheme Part 1: The Missing Cornerstone </title>
      <link>/posts/nexfv4.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 01:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nexfv4.html</guid>
      <description>Hey Everyone!
What a fucking few days hey? GME closes almost 15% up, streamers that are more interested in their weird tarot card readings than actual data, FUD that we can barely even spot anymore, and an IV increase that is being hidden by a hidden company none of us have even talked about. Wait&amp;hellip; what was that last part? Oh yeah haha, another fucking DTCC that we have all neglected or overlooked or just got buried somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[UPDATE] BlackRock is about to delete Shitadel out of existence. </title>
      <link>/posts/n2jdy6.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 14:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n2jdy6.html</guid>
      <description>Hello apes/retards,
I&amp;rsquo;d like to provide an update to my previous post (wb) which outlines the possibility that BlackRock is in the process of deleting Shitadel out of existence. As of this morning, FINRA has reported no major material changes to its list of major institutional shareholders. However, it maintains the position of BlackRock Fund Advisors at &amp;amp; around 14 million shares.
For the past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been periodically reviewing the SEC&amp;rsquo;s page on BlackRock&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary firm (wb) in the hopes that a 13G or 13F would pop up indicating of the change in ownership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merrill Lynch gave control of my retirement to a hedge fund and gave them complete authority </title>
      <link>/posts/mtftnu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 16:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtftnu.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIP /u/leavemeanon - WHERE ARE THE SHARES (Part 3) Resurrected </title>
      <link>/posts/nt8t9n.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 23:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nt8t9n.html</guid>
      <description>[Part 1] (wb)
[Part 2] (wb)
​
Hi all,
There were a lot of apes in the daily discussion thread wondering why the DD by /u/leavemeanon (wb) was gone. Turns out they&amp;rsquo;ve deleted their account for some reason, along with their posts. I did a bit of digging and managed to recover their posts (shoutout to https://camas.github.io/reddit-search (wb)), which I&amp;rsquo;ll be shamelessly reposting as there seems to be some demand:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME Calls for 4/16. A little nudge and Hedgies R Fukd. </title>
      <link>/posts/mqz8mp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 20:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mqz8mp.html</guid>
      <description>Important - See edit 2 at bottom of my write up.
A lot of calls have been added this week on top of what was already the most stacked options week for GME by far. There are no other weeks on the board that are even close to this week. The closest, in July is barely half by volume.
I&amp;rsquo;ll give the quick rundown on calls for the smooth brained and new apes to make sure you understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is this ENTIRE SUB on Adderall today!???? Geez the DD I have seen in the past hour has fucking blew me away!!! Here&#39;s a few in one post for those who might have missed them... been a bit busy myself and almost went to sleep without taking my nightly dive... </title>
      <link>/posts/n7ino0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 06:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n7ino0.html</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: As always, take everything with a grain of salt, and do your own research. Some of this is speculation and not entirely based on facts.
Enjoy getting your tetas jacked
&amp;quot; Comprehensive DD of how Citadel and friends are scamming GME and other shorts and how they are laundering the money. &amp;quot;
https://www.reddit.com/r/GME/comments/n6nr7a/comprehensive_dd_of_how_citadel_and_friends_are/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3 (wb)
links to &amp;quot; [1/3] The Ultimate DD guide to the moon!!. Crazy Melon&amp;quot;
https://www.reddit.com/r/GME/comments/n2hgxq/13_the_ultimate_dd_guide_to_the_moon_crazy_melon/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3 (wb)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DTC FORM TO CONFIRM POSESSION OF SHARES!!!! HOLY SHIT!!!! </title>
      <link>/posts/mlqk6d.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 01:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mlqk6d.html</guid>
      <description>https://www.dtcc.com/legal/issue-eligibility (wb)
has anyone seen the new UPDATED form posted by the DTCC?
FINAL EDIT!!!!: I think we might be wrong on this one. I’m sorry to kill the hype but I am thinking that this has less to do with GME. I’m not 100% sure tho, I would really like to hear from some of the credentialed big brains like u/atobitt and u/rensole. Again I am an ape just like you guys just wanted to get exposure on something that I saw as possibly huge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlackRock is about to delete Shitadel out of existence. </title>
      <link>/posts/mp7zbn.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 06:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mp7zbn.html</guid>
      <description>Hello apes/retards. I&amp;rsquo;d like to propose a theory in regards to some of the data that&amp;rsquo;s been floating around over the past few days.
So far, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen data published by FINRA (wb) which describes total equity ownership ~192%. Many people have insinuated that this % is not accurate due to duplicates of the same entity. However, you can verify that some these entities are not the same, and represent transactions from parent&amp;gt;child or entirely separate positions held by affiliates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The real price of GME is currently around 900-1k RIGHT NOW BASED ON OBV </title>
      <link>/posts/mp1sgt.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 23:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mp1sgt.html</guid>
      <description>FIRST OF ALL, I AM NOT A FINANCIAL ADVISOR. THIS IS NOT FINANCIAL ADVICE. THESE ARE JUST MY OPINIONS AND INTERPRETATION. MATTER FACT, I AM JUST POSTING PICTURES OF CRAYON SCRIBBLES.
Since I can barely read/write myself, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep this short and get straight to the point. There are way too many DD&amp;rsquo;s out there, written by apes way wiser than me, with DETAILED explanations of everything I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. SUCH AS THIS SUPER IN-DEPTH DD REGARDING OBV IF ANY SMOOTH BRAINS WANNA DEVELOP A FEW WRINKLES BY u/Cuttingwater_ : https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HEDGIES DID NOT BUY DEEP IN-THE-MONEY CALLS TODAY FOR THE FIRST TIME </title>
      <link>/posts/ml2q0p.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 03:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ml2q0p.html</guid>
      <description>Good Evening Apes,
Hope all of you are getting settled in nicely here in our new sanctuary. I remind you that you all turn this place from house into a home. Let&amp;rsquo;s get right into it.
Many of you may know me from my previous posts depicting the Deep ITM calls being bought out of the PHLX exchange. Interestingly enough, for the first time since this whole thing started, no large trades of Deep ITM calls were made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Dive into Dark Pool Trading - How they might accidentally be showing us the number of synthetic shares </title>
      <link>/posts/mv5kbm.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 01:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mv5kbm.html</guid>
      <description>Hello Apes,
Cheers to all the hedge funds forcing my brain into growing a few wrinkles! I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be here today without you! Y&amp;rsquo;all ready for that dank confirmation bias? Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to puff puff pass this on to any relevant subreddits.
​
We all &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; there is some major fudgery going on. One of the areas I personally understood the least was Dark Pools or OTC trading. I am not going to pretend I have a masters in economics or hell that I even finished college, but I can assure you I have a black belt in google and know how to operate a spreadsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>630 Million Shares WAS NOT A GLITCH </title>
      <link>/posts/mpdjwv.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 13:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mpdjwv.html</guid>
      <description>Everyone needs to read this:
https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/movevb/dance_of_darkness_the_sec_and_dark_pools/ (wb)
630 million share data confirmed by TD.
There is a tonne of great DD in this post. read it, then read it again, then understand it after reading it again.
PRO tip: on android device long hold over text, select all, select 3 dots on right, select &amp;ldquo;read aloud&amp;rdquo;
This helps me digest those extra long DDs
marked at possible DD to bring attention to the real DD linked</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>POTENTIAL DD: Banks are hiring outside consultants to reconcile their trades. I got a job description today from a recruiter to &#34;Track and resolve all open fails&#34; on behalf of their Prime Brokerage clients (i.e. hedgies and institutions) More inside... </title>
      <link>/posts/njp4pq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 04:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/njp4pq.html</guid>
      <description>So I just got an email from a recruiter with the following job description:
​
Job Title: Operations Analyst I (11874582)
Work Location: UNJ0001 525 Washington Boulevard Jersey City NJ 07310 ( Onsite job)
Rate: $43.47/hr on W2 ( We can not work on corp to corp)
Contract: Long Term Contract
Main Responsibilities:
 . Trade Comparison Clean up on all DTC unaffirmed Prime Brokerage trades, by liaising directly with Prime Brokerage Clients and executing broker’s Middle Office and Settlements teams Clean up all unmatched international (ie, non US trades), by liaising directly with Prime Brokerage Clients and executing broker’s Middle Office and Settlements teams Fail Monitoring Track and resolve all open fails, by liaising with Prime Brokerage clients, internal settlements teams, executing broker’s Middle Office and Settlements teams, Corporate actions and stock loan trading desk and operations Trade Amendments and Static data updates Make appropriate amendments and corrections to US and non US trades to amend misbookings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THEORY: Glacier and other &#34;new&#34; HFs are just shells where Citadel has been hiding their FTD/put game. Regulatory cycle is now revealing them slowly, and they want us to SeLl WhEn HFs Go BaNkRuPt. We ain&#39;t selling til YOU go bankrupt Kenny! </title>
      <link>/posts/nf8nsd.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 11:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nf8nsd.html</guid>
      <description>See the edits at the end if you want to follow a trail of DDs that leads us here.
This is just a theory. But we know that Citadel has been hiding FTDs in some kind of married put shenanigans, so maybe they have a way to use these shell companies to hide an even greater short position than we can even tell from their activity alone.
Look how Melvin hid their positions for two months by asking for a secret filing even when they knew they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiple SEC whistleblowers awarded on the same day we got the Melvin loss news </title>
      <link>/posts/mohp16.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mohp16.html</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I am an ape who just learned how to form complete sentences. Please provide any counter evidence to the following theory.
There&amp;rsquo;s a lot out there that the 49% loss on Melvin seems sus in regards to timing and the seemingly &amp;ldquo;too good news&amp;rdquo; especially with the way things have been going. Several OPs suggest that this could be a distraction or a setup for a fake squeeze soon. Both are entirely plausible and I am currently attempting to scour additional records to see if something was swept under the rug and not picked up by MSM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed: 32 floor is Ken Griffin’s Shitadel. Lower floors: JP Morgan Chase. Middle floors: Attorney’s offices </title>
      <link>/posts/mtddmi.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtddmi.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hank helping you understand why MM/HFs would take these crazy risks </title>
      <link>/posts/n42suk.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 18:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n42suk.html</guid>
      <description>*********** I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice ************
Salutations, apes.
Last night, as I was listening to Carly Rae Jepson&amp;rsquo;s smash hit &amp;ldquo;Azz &amp;amp; Tittiez&amp;rdquo; in my race care bed, a thought came to me: hedies r fuk. Then I woke up to my wife yelling at me to pay her boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s rent. I immediately apologized to both of them and bought him flowers and chocolates so he knows that I care about him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dance of Darkness: The SEC and Dark Pools </title>
      <link>/posts/movevb.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 17:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/movevb.html</guid>
      <description>Dance of Darkness: The SEC and Dark Pools Hello everyone, as requested I am trying again to get this on r/Superstonk so this stays documented, and allows the light of transparency to be shone upon Darkpools, hopefully this time it uploads, and if it does, enjoy:
Hello everyone, thank you in advance for your patience and for reading this thesis on dark pools and the SEC. First, please note that this is strictly not financial advice and just research I have compiled over weeks for entertainment purposes—it&amp;rsquo;s all-public information and not intended to affect the price action of any stock in any way, shape, or form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Options data proves hedgefunds need to bankrupt GME or they will go bust. </title>
      <link>/posts/mo7t8c.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 16:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mo7t8c.html</guid>
      <description>TLDR - Options data show that the hedgefunds are still fucked and the original plan for bankrupting GME hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed. Since I&amp;rsquo;ve become more active on reddit either making posts, commenting more or responding to DMs I&amp;rsquo;ve started getting threatening messages and &amp;ldquo;insulting&amp;rdquo; comments, these do not bother me and the tone of my posts will now include a lot more sarcasm and mocking in response, please enjoy.
​
Ape. Are you struggling with the weekend?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Institutions own 74% of Jeffries Financial Group (JEF). Look who is their top Holders. BlackRock &amp; Vanguard. Also just last week Jeffries Filed for a new SPAC with the SEC. Perhaps BR &amp; Vanguard are making their move? </title>
      <link>/posts/nrwju5.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 04:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nrwju5.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DD: Here&#39;s what happens if there is over voting (more shares voted than issued) </title>
      <link>/posts/mya2a8.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 15:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mya2a8.html</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this DD is to look at the outcome if there are many more votes cast at the shareholder meeting than GME shares that are issued and outstanding. I have a background in corporate and securities law, but this is not legal advice (for GME or for apes). Just a recording of one random apes research on a topic of this ape’s own interest.
The assumption for this DD is that there will be more votes cast or otherwise represented at the shareholder meeting than GME shares that are issued and outstanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I just found out Citadel hired ex-SEC director Stephen Luparello in 2017 to be their General Counsel... and then they did all this shit... with an ex-SEC director counseling them. 😂😂😂🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🌙 </title>
      <link>/posts/nsoiq7.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 05:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nsoiq7.html</guid>
      <description>I found this article from 2017 about Citadel hiring an ex-SEC director (wb).
I found it because I saw a fellow ape say &amp;ldquo;if the SEC knew about this shit and did nothing, then the market is fooked.&amp;rdquo;
And I thought, &amp;ldquo;hmm, how do I explain to this ape that of course they know. How? For instance, a ton of them work on Wall Street. Oh! I know. I&amp;rsquo;ll search to see if anyone from the SEC works at Citadel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Calm Before Ignition: Why Low Volume, Sideways Trading Is Great </title>
      <link>/posts/mm82qt.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 18:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mm82qt.html</guid>
      <description>TLDR; Long Whales are working the Max Pain Channel; IV + consolidation is approaching levels last seen before GME rose from $4 to $350. The Low Volume and Sideways trading is aligning the stars for a Gamma booster, into the short squeeze launch from a $1,000 platform. Enjoy this beautiful calm before ignition; sleeping soundly tonight, knowing Kenny G isn&amp;rsquo;t.
 Last week I published a report on why Long Whales are orchestrating this channel $175-198 around Max Pain in options market and how it is designed to bleed the Hedge Funds of the funds they have left: Our Whale is Suppressing Volatility to Bleed HFs &amp;ndash; Max Pain Explained (wb)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/6/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. Storm chasers edition. </title>
      <link>/posts/mlbjk9.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 13:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mlbjk9.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 172, 176.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.5, 218, 226, 230, 234, 243, 250, 253, 256.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Believe BlackRock HAS THEIR FINGER ON THE BUTTON OF OUR MOASS... </title>
      <link>/posts/mksku6.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 19:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mksku6.html</guid>
      <description>From previous DD, we&amp;rsquo;ve discovered
1.) BlackRock has the most shares in both AMC/GME, (Marketbeat (wb))
2.) They have a strong relationship tie to Adam Aron (wb), CEO of AMC
3.) They hold their &amp;ldquo;highest level of cash in years (wb)&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; [Please watch that video if you want to understand my BlackRock CIO references]
**4) Ryan Cohen &amp;amp; Chewy received $350MIL in six rounds of funding (wb), one of which was BlackRock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Imminent Liquidity Crisis &amp; Reverse Repos Usage - Smooth Brain Edition </title>
      <link>/posts/nhepn1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 23:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nhepn1.html</guid>
      <description>Intro: Many of us Apes have been hearing about Reverse Repos and the liquidity crisis as of late, but some may not understand what that means or looks like, and I&amp;rsquo;m going to explain it &amp;amp; show the relevant data as simply and clearly as possible so that even a brain as smooth as a watermelon could form a wrinkle or two. Technical explanations/suit jargon are simplified by the emojis 🍌🦍</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch ape here. This is the WTC in Amsterdam. we have a curfew here that forbids people to be outside of their homes after 2200. and somehow they are all at their work on a sunday. APES.... this is happening </title>
      <link>/posts/mtj7ui.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 19:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtj7ui.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counter DD: NY Fed $400 bln reverse repos is not tied to margin calls. It&#39;s worse. </title>
      <link>/posts/nbt1sp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 22:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nbt1sp.html</guid>
      <description>Changed May 16th: Please see Update at bottom of post. Today there is hype about an Italian financial news site reporting that the New York Fed has lent 400 billion USD to 39 financial institutes over the past two days. It concludes that big Wall Street parties have been margin called and are panic borrowing from the Fed to make margin. Link: https://www.money.it/Fed-repo-miliardi-Wall-Street (wb)
None of it is correct.
TL;DR</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Final Update] Superstonk users ALONE hold between 27 million and 35 million shares. No, really. </title>
      <link>/posts/mzuodo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 18:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mzuodo.html</guid>
      <description>TL:DR; after doing two polls and comparing to another user&amp;rsquo;s results, I estimate superstonk users own between 27 million and 35 million shares of GME.
Edit: A very large point of misunderstanding is that the average shares are too high. In statistics, averages are easily skewed by outliers. For example, you have two groups: 3,3,3,2,4,2,4,3 and another 0,0,1,2,10,2,3,4. The average of both is 3. People have said it&amp;rsquo;s impossible for the average person to own $25-30k worth of shares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMPORTANT: Gamestop 2020 Annual Report, Official Links, and 🦍🦍🦍🦍🦍 (aka YOU) </title>
      <link>/posts/n0mx43.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 19:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n0mx43.html</guid>
      <description>​
EDITS:
 in my haste to get this message out to all you apes, my title incorrectly says 2020 Annual Report&amp;hellip; it should say 2021 Annual Report is CORRECTLY referring to the 2020 Annual Report that will be filed in 2021, not the 2019 Annual Report that was filed in 2020, in response to some questions/comments by apes in this and other posts. Thank you u/hdeck for catching that. This is what happens when I take a quick break from work to update the community&amp;hellip; 😅 u/HolyPhoenician &amp;amp; u/TheKingOfLimbs made excellent points in the comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to expect 6/9 at the shareholder&#39;s meeting </title>
      <link>/posts/nqwvgq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 21:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nqwvgq.html</guid>
      <description>Hi All,
Now that the we are just 7 days away from the shareholder&amp;rsquo;s meeting scheduled for 6/9 I wanted to share some thoughts on what we can possibly expect from the meeting itself.
Gamestop confirmed the meeting for 6/9 at 11am EST and will conclude at 11:15 EST. Dont expect any big announcements during the meeting especially since its only 15 minutes. What usually happens in these meetings is the company will announce the PRELIMINARY results to the proxy vote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MOASS is not a straight line up, do not paper hand at a minor dip </title>
      <link>/posts/njd8au.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 18:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/njd8au.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It is said that if you know your enemies and know yourself, you will not be imperilled in a hundred battles;&amp;rdquo; -Sun Tzu
There are several areas where the MOASS could be hindered. Saying the MOASS will be one straight line up is FUD because people will paperhand the moment it goes down. However, these things may or may not happen, so if you day trade, there is a very large chance you get left behind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The final nail for Citadel – And you’re holding the HAMMER!!! 🚀 </title>
      <link>/posts/nghov2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nghov2.html</guid>
      <description>This is a summary of what we have discovered:
🍌
Citadel adds a new branch to hide certain holdings (Ashler)
Obtains a large portion of Freddie Mac (percent not known)
Some insane shit goes down in January with their books
Major drama and defaults happen, all connected to Citadel
New rules are passed by the govt in record time because Citadel is way too connected to the housing market/ commercial properties</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Cohens Kill Shot....the Reverse Merger </title>
      <link>/posts/n7bv2h.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 23:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n7bv2h.html</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s RC plan, does he have a plan?
​
Here is what I think Ryan Cohens plan is
Ok I have heard allot of talk about stock splits, reverse splits, dividends or crypto dividends ect on how RC can shake the shorts.
None of those really go the whole way. Reverse split is out of the question as the stock is not liquid enough, and there is legal questions surrounding the crypto dividend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME human psychology </title>
      <link>/posts/n0de5w.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 12:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n0de5w.html</guid>
      <description>This post probably will get down vote to oblivion but fk it, I can&amp;rsquo;t be the only one feel like this.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been with GME since October last year and seeing how the og of this play versus now is kind of scary to say the least.
I wasn&amp;rsquo;t as early as DFV or Cohen but I got in because I make bet based on people and after literally watching every RC&amp;rsquo;s interview and reading every article I went all in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is an exemple of a short squeeze: DGAZF, stock&#39;s price shoot from $125 to $25&#39;000 in August 2020 </title>
      <link>/posts/mv1n9x.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 22:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mv1n9x.html</guid>
      <description>not financial advice
For people saying that there was a reverse split and that is not a good exemple. Can you provide your source stating this happening in august 2020? The only reverse split I see was in 2018 and thus is irrelevant. The price which shoot from $125 to $25&#39;000 is still a &amp;ldquo;true price&amp;rdquo;
I saw this post saying the fact:
 https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/mu68w9/recent_example_of_the_potential_we_have_here/ (wb) Credit to u/prophetprofiteer  Why the hell the post above didn&amp;rsquo;t moon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reposting - GME and the Market Crash </title>
      <link>/posts/mvaaa7.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 07:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvaaa7.html</guid>
      <description>I posted this almost 2 months ago and folks thought I was wrong or fear mongering. Look at all the DD now and tell me I&amp;rsquo;m wrong. I wish I was wrong because this is a big deal as most of you have learned. Either way, we are going to the fucking moon and beyond!!! Enjoy your tendies when they come because you&amp;rsquo;re going to be the apes who survived it and earned it for holding throughout all the bullshit so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DFV UNO CATS TWEET DECODED: 4/16/21 is gonna be WILD, 5 trading days remaining </title>
      <link>/posts/mnqdym.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 20:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mnqdym.html</guid>
      <description>Hi ape detectives! Today me (Watson) and our resident Sherlock u/Jerrynka69 bring you a solution to the most recent DFV tweet ( UNO Kitty DFV Tweet (wb) ), cryptically sending us a message like only he, The One Who Is Not a Cat can.
 Firstly, we&amp;rsquo;ll pay attention to highlighted cards which have been edited in. There&amp;rsquo;s 2 decks, one on the left side in hand and one on the right side, probably a discard pile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theory on the FTD Loop Missing Link - a T&#43;35 surge followed by an infinite T&#43;21 loop surrounding specific option dates. Support for April 16th options T&#43;21 theory pointing to a possible surge tomorrow, or T&#43;35 surge on May 24th </title>
      <link>/posts/nf22qz.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 05:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nf22qz.html</guid>
      <description>Preface ==========  I&amp;rsquo;m not a financial advisor. .
Speculative post? OR REAL SHIT? I&amp;rsquo;m pretty hyped about April 16th being a doomsday clock for the hedgies, since that&amp;rsquo;s the time they started working the night shift. &amp;ldquo;Give it up for day 15!&amp;rdquo; as Mr. Krabs would say.
Do you like dates? I like dates. I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to take you on one. Just ask. 😉
I would like apes to pick at this, because I feel like we&amp;rsquo;re really close to finding the secret sauce to the price movements and predicting the next surge (maybe even MOASS ignition).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon, Bain Capital and Citadel Bust Out the Competition </title>
      <link>/posts/np33hr.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 13:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/np33hr.html</guid>
      <description>What is a bust out?
In a bust-out scheme, the identity and credit line of a business are used to obtain loans and goods with no intention of repayment. In some instances, businesses are created for this sole purpose; in others, legitimate businesses are acquired and used for the fraud.
https://www.computerworld.com/article/2535189/opinion--bust-out-schemes-are-a-fraud-designed-to-make-you-go-bust.html (wb)
In this post I will go over what I believe is a scheme set out by Amazon to capture and kill companies for market share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/14/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. Hump Day! </title>
      <link>/posts/mqqgqy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 13:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mqqgqy.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 165.5, 172, 174, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚀GME and the Art of Floors🚀 (Why 1 million is not as crazy as it might seem) </title>
      <link>/posts/mlscva.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 02:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mlscva.html</guid>
      <description>Hello there fellow apes. I have decided that with a new sub should come new DD and so I have decided to write this article. Now some of you may remember me from my last article where I talked about the suspicious amount of companies that went bankrupt under the rule of the ousted members who may or may not have been planted there in order to insure GMEs failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This sub just went from 85,000 users online to 24,000 in a span of 5 minutes. </title>
      <link>/posts/no2mm0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/no2mm0.html</guid>
      <description>After this week and seeing the massive presence of members of the sub, I’ve been keeping track of how many users are online. The peak of this was 197,000 but we’ve been averaging about 150,000 for about two days straight. Today, the number has slowly declined to about 80,000 about 15 minutes ago. All of a sudden it dropped to 24,000 at 11:20PM. It’s safe to say that most likely 100,000 accounts here are either bots or old accounts used by shills to maintain an online presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Option Chains Going Crazy </title>
      <link>/posts/mq13t7.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 12:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mq13t7.html</guid>
      <description>Good morning Apes
Expect fuckery. This is a CRAZY week on the options side. The hedgies absolutely cannot lose control of the price this week, they will use every trick and cheat that exists this week.
I don’t think this is a week where anyone is worried about max pain. This is a week where hedgies just need the price as low as they can get it to avoid those call options going ITM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Bank of America Gamestop DD </title>
      <link>/posts/nsioql.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 23:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nsioql.html</guid>
      <description>TL/DR It&amp;rsquo;s possible that Bank of America is holding the biggest bag in the Gamestop saga
Note: This is just a theory, and I am not advocating anyone to do anything with their BofA accounts. Just some information I found and felt an obligation to share. I am not a financial advisor.
​
 If you owe the bank $100 that&amp;rsquo;s your problem. If you owe the bank $100 million billion, that&amp;rsquo;s the bank&amp;rsquo;s problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚨🚨🚨 Hedgies are pumping &amp; dumping penny stocks to raise capital to fight us! 🚨🚨🚨 </title>
      <link>/posts/mpeouv.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mpeouv.html</guid>
      <description>TL;DR - Hedge funds are manipulating penny stocks by exploiting the OTC market and using a pump and dump strategy to raise funds in their war against us.
 So I have strong evidence to suggest that hedgies are pumping &amp;amp; dumping penny stocks to keep a constant inflow of cash to fight their war against us.
I came about this from skimming through the FINRA OTC data.
At first, I started to look at December data, because I wanted to see if hedge funds were trading penny stocks on inside information, by trading OTC the volume and price isn&amp;rsquo;t affected on the charts and they can essentially trade behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[UPDATE] DD: I did the math. Latest Nordnet and Avanza ownership numbers confirming what we already knew: WE OWN THE FLOAT! </title>
      <link>/posts/nnngl6.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 13:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nnngl6.html</guid>
      <description>Update 1st June 2021:
RIP to my inbox, however I managed to go through all messages and updated my table accordingly, main changes listed here:
-&amp;gt; (New) T212 total shareholders available
-&amp;gt; (Updated) eToro numbers. Apparently 96k GME investors (wb) on eToro !
-&amp;gt; (Updated) Selfwealth (wb) total number of GME shareholder available.
I encourage all of you apes to go and ask your broker for data available. Shares per ape, total shares held, total shareholders, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Found another shill vegetable. don&#39;t eat that shit, it&#39;s poison for Apes </title>
      <link>/posts/mrefso.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mrefso.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So the SEC have told Stock Brokers as of the 22nd April they must have the capital on hand to cover every share they borrowed from investors and lent to hedge funds. </title>
      <link>/posts/msy5yf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 20:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/msy5yf.html</guid>
      <description>( Its important to recognize that this IS NOT a rule or regulation, it is a staff statement. Not saying nothing will come of this or it won&amp;rsquo;t be acted on, but we can&amp;rsquo;t take this to mean it&amp;rsquo;s a rule that will be enforced.)
The letter is an internal letter, what you may understand is basically that its similar to a &amp;ldquo;Disclaimer&amp;rdquo; written at the bottom of internal memos, letters etc, stating that the letter in itself is not a new actionable regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trade Fuckery Update - Vanishing trades, Compared to other stocks, now I have even less idea what the fuck is going on. </title>
      <link>/posts/nk02x0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 15:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nk02x0.html</guid>
      <description>This is an update from my post last week, which can be found here: https://old.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/nhyzk0/been_waiting_for_this_opportunity_trade_fuckery/
Ok, this morning&amp;rsquo;s first 15 minutes was a pretty good control sample, as it shows a big price push down, bouncing off $180, then passing it, then beginning the push down again:
   Time of Candle Trades on ATP Trades after Refresh Difference Percentage Reduced     9:31 62017 47494 14523 23.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thankyou for Flying GME , Please Grab your final tickets.... and Remember to put your Helmets on. ===Now Boarding=== </title>
      <link>/posts/naktm8.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 09:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/naktm8.html</guid>
      <description>There are movements happening all over the Market 24 hours&amp;hellip; more volume and Volatility than there ever has been.
I Love Bollinger Bands&amp;hellip; google it if you want to know more, Im not your Mom!
There is a massive incoming upward push on GME (yeah yeah you all know &amp;hellip; already)
This is confirmation&amp;hellip; that last prickling doubt telling you maybe it wont work?.. what happens if?
Well it will&amp;hellip;and it is&amp;hellip; and if your reading this your probably knee deep in shit and paddling like a toddler in a ball pool like the rest of us anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME Magnum Opus update: The day of reckoning </title>
      <link>/posts/mvdk5a.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 11:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvdk5a.html</guid>
      <description>CRUCIAL UPDATE: If my theory is correct, I will be renaming this &amp;ldquo;the theory of hank&amp;rdquo;
EDIT 1: Looking similar to 1/13: low volume to start but no morning dip. Look to 10-11 for some action if we see any today.
EDIT 2: ooooooo look, new format. Uncle Hank will now be updating on the top instead of the bottom. Is this new format confirmation that the squeeze is imminent?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put Anomalies PT1 — Were 127 MILLION&#43; SYNTHETIC SHARES created since January, or is this data ‘nothing to worry about’? Why were 1.094 MILLION worthless PUTS traded on March3&amp;4? Was it linked to the open interest? Findings of a 2-week market-data-driven and white paper investigation. </title>
      <link>/posts/mz7c7h.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 20:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mz7c7h.html</guid>
      <description>Tl;Dr: Not this time. You won&amp;rsquo;t regret the time spent on this. There is also an ELIA at the bottom. Disclaimer: The aim of the post is to display some options trading data that I believe many of us haven’t seen. It is to contextualize abnormal options trading activity on GME and dispel some myths about the put open interest.
BY NO MEANS DO I INTEND TO MAKE CONCRETE STATEMENTS ABOUT WHAT THIS DATA MEANS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never a Borrower Be: A synopsis of GME&#39;s 1% Borrow Rate </title>
      <link>/posts/ntpkuy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 16:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ntpkuy.html</guid>
      <description>Hello Superstonk!
I just wanted to do another compilation this weekend. Re-iterating some old DD I have written as it starts to become applicable to the current situation.
Jefferies and BOA coming out this week and declaring no more short positions would be allowed to be taken, added some weight to a thesis I had come up with a few weeks ago. I was getting frequently asked on reddit and YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/19/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. Up 11% premarket! THE GREAT CLIMB </title>
      <link>/posts/mu0gte.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 13:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mu0gte.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 158.5, 162.5, 163, 165.5, 172, 174, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There is a WAR to control the DTCC and GME is the BATTLEGROUND: Citadel &amp; Co VS JPM/BOA &amp; Co: Why isn&#39;t anyone talking about this??? </title>
      <link>/posts/mouj57.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mouj57.html</guid>
      <description>EDIT 1:
First of all, thank you to everyone who has awarded and commented on this post. Honestly, I thought that only 500-700ish people would read this, so the fact that it got this much traction is a surprise.
Secondly, I just want to say that this is all speculation based on some research I did into the figures behind the DTCC. There are most likely things I&amp;rsquo;ve missed, misunderstood, or got wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The SR-NSCC-2021-801 CAN be approved AUTOMATICALLY this week. (MAY THE 4TH BE WITH YOU). </title>
      <link>/posts/n3gxsq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 21:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n3gxsq.html</guid>
      <description>Sorry for my english I don&amp;rsquo;t want to post missinformation, so please if something is wrong in this post please tell me and I will correct.  Last friday reading this SEC WANTS US TO GIVE THEM ONE CHANCE (wb).
Full SEC speech: SEC (wb).
The TLDR done by u/Firetorpedos is very nice.
 TLDR On April 28th, the SEC website published a speech that has NOT recieved its due attention from apes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIP /u/leavemeanon - WHERE ARE THE SHARES (Part 1) Resurrected </title>
      <link>/posts/nt8ot8.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 23:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nt8ot8.html</guid>
      <description>[Part 2] (wb)
[Part 3] (wb)
​
Hi all,
There were a lot of apes in the daily discussion thread wondering why the DD by /u/leavemeanon was gone. Turns out they&amp;rsquo;ve deleted their account for some reason, along with their posts. I did a bit of digging and managed to recover their posts (shoutout to https://camas.github.io/reddit-search (wb)), which I&amp;rsquo;ll be shamelessly reposting as there seems to be some demand:
​</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the Squeeze is Squoze USE A LIMIT SELL NOT A MARKET SELL! </title>
      <link>/posts/mrnswq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 20:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mrnswq.html</guid>
      <description>APES!
The price you see on your broker is the average price between the bid and the ask. The bid is set by the buyers and the ask is set by the sellers. The market makers (Shitadel and others) make their money on the difference. The more liquid a security (which GME isn&amp;rsquo;t at all, hence the extremely low volume and blatant manipulation) the tighter the spread between the Bid and the Ask.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvard Professor Explains Why January Was The &#34;Baby Squeeze&#34;, What&#39;s Happening With FTDs, and The DTCC Insurance Policy </title>
      <link>/posts/mlasep.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mlasep.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where there is smoke, there is fire </title>
      <link>/posts/mvj8fz.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 16:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvj8fz.html</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: Too much is going on right now in the financial world for it all NOT to be connected. And if Michael Bury and other financial experts are right, then the United States and other countries across the globe will soon be in a dire economic situation akin to the Great Depression. Where there is smoke, there is fire. This truly isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;original DD&amp;rdquo; as it is an easy source to find all the information relevant to a pretty common conclusion many of this sub are making;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wargame Theory II: The Mother of All FUD (MOAFUD) </title>
      <link>/posts/ng4ja0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 12:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ng4ja0.html</guid>
      <description>Blanderson Snooper here, back with another page of toilet reading for all you Apes. Does an Ape shit in the woods? Only if there&amp;rsquo;s wifi.
If you want a shot of feel-good confirmation bias, skip to the last section, &amp;ldquo;The Good News.&amp;rdquo; See you back here in a minute. If you&amp;rsquo;re ready to take the whole wild ride, buckle up and enjoy.
🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀
Four weeks ago I published the Wargame Theory (wb), a cultural DD that used narrative as a way to explain some of the unexplainable parts of the GME saga.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/8/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. CHARIMAN EDITION </title>
      <link>/posts/mmrmpy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 13:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mmrmpy.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 172, 174, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.5, 218, 226, 230, 234, 243, 250, 253, 256.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/7/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. </title>
      <link>/posts/mm21by.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 13:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mm21by.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 172, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.5, 218, 226, 230, 234, 243, 250, 253, 256.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Been waiting for this opportunity - Trade fuckery - 37% of trades disappearing during 10 minute block between 1:30 and 1:39. </title>
      <link>/posts/nhyzk0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 18:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nhyzk0.html</guid>
      <description>So, we all knew today was going to be a battle for the $180 point because of the options expiry on this date. Lo and behold, right before we got to the $180 marker at 1:30, we got pushed down pretty intensely.
Now, we had seen a few weeks back a bunch of negative trades at settlement in after hours at 4:15, and then suddenly that stopped. But when the trade volume was exceptionally low, we kept seeing trades disappearing from minute to minute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well, look what gets published tomorrow! This prevents Shitadel from selling underneath the NBBO by using crossed and locked orders. Or something. This was discussed in DD last week. </title>
      <link>/posts/mqisex.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 04:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mqisex.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Food DD - 2008 vs 2021 - A possible indicator that shit is hitting the fan//Confirmation Bias//I saw an ape suggest watching &#34;Inside Job&#34; and I saw something! </title>
      <link>/posts/n395pq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 15:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n395pq.html</guid>
      <description>Dear Apes
I am watching a documentary on Amazon Prime called &amp;ldquo;The Inside Job&amp;rdquo;. I have not finished watching it, I just stopped it to run over to my laptop and check something.
In that documentary, the reason banks were able to do all sorts of wacky bullshit - First selling collateralized debt obligations (CDOs), which were all the bad mortgages packaged into a high quality McHappy Meal, then later betting against CDOs - was because of essentially bribing regulatory bodies to give them a high rating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABN AMRO headquarters in Amsterdam - Top floor fully lit on Sunday night. My wife just drove me here. pic is 1 hour ago. Credit to the guys who found the Google &#34;busy&#34; data </title>
      <link>/posts/mtkv4u.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 20:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtkv4u.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The entire Citadel building is GLOWING at 4:30 am Sunday morning per hotel manager i just called. It confirms this pic. </title>
      <link>/posts/mt91xx.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mt91xx.html</guid>
      <description>Pic of the GLOWING building
He says it is never glowing this late. He thought it was strange even before i called him!
I found the hotel using Google Maps cuz i went on a hunt for an ape friendly eye-witness confirmation that could confirm whether this is typical. “This is STRANGE!” he said. “The building never glows this late. It is glowing.” He was a foreigner. These were his words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/12/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. We go up or down? </title>
      <link>/posts/mpdrjq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 13:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mpdrjq.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 172, 174, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.5, 218, 226, 230, 234, 243, 250, 253, 256.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T&#43;21 FTD squeeze is happening???? </title>
      <link>/posts/mvtpne.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvtpne.html</guid>
      <description>*******Edit 3: last edit, my post you’ll see I added incorrectly with tomorrow’s date NOT being T+21, that would be Friday 4/23! My initial post I had the 3rd squeeze date as 3/24 by mistake, therefore my day prediction is 1 day off. 4/23 would be the next FTD squeeze! ****** I AM THINKING 4/23 WE SEE SOME GREEN DILDOS
*****Edit 3.1: haha damn okay, I’m seeing a lot of 4/26 being the 21st trading day after&amp;hellip;so in my smooth brain I included the day of the run up in the calculation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Exactly Happened with Melvin Capital? </title>
      <link>/posts/n090ge.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 06:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n090ge.html</guid>
      <description>Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ve been typing all day and sipping coffee all night, so strap in for my crayon drawings.
Citadel and Point72 have owned at least 51% (controlling interest) in Melvin Capital since January 24th (through a private placement investment/unregistered offering) following Melvin receiving notice that their broker/dealer had margin called them. Let me explain.
https://www.reuters.com/article/us-retail-trading-melvin/melvin-capital-ends-month-with-over-8-billion-in-assets-after-investors-added-cash-source-idUSKBN2A00KW (wb)
Not that I think anyone should read or trust Reuters (or any source for that matter, even me) but they have been an interesting source to evaluate since January.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Just a Bug, Bro Part 7: It&#39;s Actually a Simulation </title>
      <link>/posts/n1j3nz.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 01:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n1j3nz.html</guid>
      <description>Holy Fuck.
This is probably one of the bigger things I have figured out so far.
I sifted through every Citadel Advisors LLC SEC Filing since the squeeze began (I have the spreadsheets to show it) and figured out some fucked up things (oh and I figured out who Suspecthanna is operating as - and they are doing the same thing as Shitadel).
​
Im going to blow your mind like our moms should have done to our dads instead of letting him finish in her and bringing all of us into this clown pyramid scheme we are living it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Merger, Naked Shorts &amp; Covering: The Golden Bullet </title>
      <link>/posts/nnt97f.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 18:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nnt97f.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot; Once that CUSIP changes, the naked shorter has no apparent way to close out the naked short position. No stock under the old CUSIP number exists anymore; it all automatically converts to the new CUSIP. &amp;quot; UPDATE AT BOTTOM: CUSIP CHANGE IS INCONCLUSIVE TO FORCE NAKEDS TO COVER. LOOKS LIKE WE NEED CRYPTO DIVIDEND FOR THIS STEP. EXPLANATION BELOW.
Why a Reverse Merger is the Golden Bullet: (if on mobile, scroll right on table)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/9/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. Playing the waiting game. </title>
      <link>/posts/mnh3oq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 13:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mnh3oq.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 172, 174, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.5, 218, 226, 230, 234, 243, 250, 253, 256.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DD?? WTF HOW THIS IS NOT THE MOST UPVOTED POST EVER?? ANYONE HERE KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT THIS???? NEED HELP TO UNDERSTAND.... </title>
      <link>/posts/mkvvae.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 21:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mkvvae.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚀🚀🚀 The Shell Game III – Lifting the Final Cups for Take-Off. </title>
      <link>/posts/myn9vn.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 02:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/myn9vn.html</guid>
      <description>🚀🚀🚀 The Shell Game III – Lifting the Final Cups. The Shell Game
In [Shell Game I] (https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/mvvmvp/time_to_expose_the_shell_game_ftds_can_be_reset/) and Shell Game II(wb) you have seen that I am convinced other well-supported DD theories (such as deep-ITM Calls) do not come close to dealing with the full FTD problem that exists in the system. As I detailed in Shell Game II, ETFs containing GME featured extremely bizarre FTD data, much like our favorite stock, GME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONNECTING THE DOTS: GOOGLE SAYING CITADEL HQ BUSY AFTER HOURS &amp; US TREASURY ANNOUNCING FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS MONEY LAUNDERING via CRYPTOCURRENCY! </title>
      <link>/posts/mt7gpk.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 06:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mt7gpk.html</guid>
      <description>U.S. TREASURY TO CHARGE SEVERAL FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS FOR MONEY LAUNDERING USING CRYPTOCURRENCIES -SOURCES (wb)
 Reddit: Google Maps showig activity in Citadel HQ (wb).
Google Maps link to Citadel HQ (wb).
On Google Maps it appears there was activity (and a lot, simply a few phones wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have triggered Google to say there was activity at the HQ) at Citadel&amp;rsquo;s HQ after hours.
 Cryptocurrencies just took a MASSIVE dump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin and possibly all crypto has potentially been our canary in the coal mine </title>
      <link>/posts/mteyvy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 15:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mteyvy.html</guid>
      <description>Gonna keep this short and sweet
After noticing the Crypto crash last night I got hit with a series of &amp;ldquo;It was just a simple 10 BIllions margin call, happens all the time&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;China had a black out and erased billions of dollars&amp;rdquo; or my favorite &amp;ldquo;This is crypto, just zoom out&amp;rdquo;. So you know what I did? I zoomed out.
There have been 4 other spikes downward in Bitcoin before this one and they&amp;rsquo;ve all been this year after the huge run up that started in Dec 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The EVERYTHING Short - Mortgage Edition </title>
      <link>/posts/ml39bx.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 04:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ml39bx.html</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is not financial advice, I am not a financial advisor, please take everything I say with a grain of salt and do your own due diligence research.
[Edit 1] - Woah this blew up. Just woke up on the west coast, will try to answer questions/respond to comments. However, I do want to point out that I plan to iterate this DD as holes / counter points are brought up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 26th Update on the Married-Put Forensic Analysis - Shorts all the way down </title>
      <link>/posts/nl90c5.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 05:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nl90c5.html</guid>
      <description>T&amp;rsquo;was the night before MOASS&amp;rsquo;mas and if you&amp;rsquo;re too jacked to sleep, I have something to keep you jacked until Market Open.
Following up to my post from last week, here (wb).
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already that, this business about Married-Put-Remnants and Irrational-Puts won&amp;rsquo;t make much sense, so go catch up and then pop back here after, kthxbye!
Last week, on Days of our Lives Buying and Hodling &amp;hellip;
We saw about 75k Irrational Puts expire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/13/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. The waiting game. </title>
      <link>/posts/mq262c.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 13:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mq262c.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 172, 174, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.5, 218, 226, 230, 234, 243, 250, 253, 256.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT IS TIME: We must fully prepare ourselves for the MOASS and this is how. </title>
      <link>/posts/mnfmrh.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 11:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mnfmrh.html</guid>
      <description>Okay Apes, The DD has been done, The DD has been consumed by apes and there has been no rebuttal to the facts of our DD anywhere. There is new stuff coming out but by now we all should know that it is inevitable. The MOASS could happen any day now. There are a lot of possible catalysts approaching fast that each on their own could launch us to Andromeda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/20/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. I&#39;m taking a leave of absence for a while. </title>
      <link>/posts/muq664.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 13:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/muq664.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 158.5, 162.5, 163, 165.5, 172, 174, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEC wants us to give them ONE chance. </title>
      <link>/posts/n2e9t9.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 08:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n2e9t9.html</guid>
      <description>Actual post is below under the line, here is a long edit in response to FUD-packers.
EDIT: Thank you SO much for response, i am overwhelmed and titjacked from your feedback! Thanks!
In response to some FUDPOSTERS arguing to the point that this is not an official SEC communication. Well duh. The first line in this post is clearly saying whats up: &amp;ldquo;its a speech published on SEC website&amp;rdquo;. The speech partially describes what SEC is up to, like LIBOR-stuff and the coming meme-stock report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROCKET FUEL: Kenny&#39;s running out of resources and shorting everything to pay for it. </title>
      <link>/posts/mwm2iz.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 03:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mwm2iz.html</guid>
      <description>​
https://preview.redd.it/zk82vsmg5vu61.jpg?width=546&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=66d8ab9a141b356db41c28d89929216475236ca5
TL;DR: Margin is calling. Below is a list of a bunch of other stocks that SPECIFICALLY CITADEL is shorting into oblivion to make money to pay for their debt. Oh, by the way, it&amp;rsquo;s not working out for them.
Not financial advice. I just like the stock. All of them.
I&amp;rsquo;ll keep this short and sweet, it&amp;rsquo;s just a bunch of Ortex/FINRA data on stocks that Citadel is MASS PRINTING to make their money back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONCE AGAIN NO IN-THE-MONEY CALLS WERE PURCHASED TODAY </title>
      <link>/posts/mlt726.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 03:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mlt726.html</guid>
      <description>Apes,
As they like to say in the business: No news is good news. Today I bring you not a single ounce of news regarding these deep in the money calls. Not even so much as a peep out of the HF&amp;rsquo;s buying these calls.
This officially rules out the idea that yesterday was just some crazy coincidence. The time of covering FTD&amp;rsquo;s with Deep ITM calls has come to an end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting GME&#39;s Price Action With Elliot Waves 4/29 🚀 </title>
      <link>/posts/n0qnpv.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n0qnpv.html</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s poppin apes, u/possibly6 here with some bias that I indeed can confirm will confirm your bias. confirmed.
As always, this aint no mothafuckin financial advice, hoe. The views expressed here are solely my approach to investing in this specific equity. I ape an am.
obligatory.
To preface, for any new apes, I am a daily technical trader. I make a living by identifying patterns and executing trades based solely on what I see on my charts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beginning of the end </title>
      <link>/posts/nbe55w.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 11:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nbe55w.html</guid>
      <description>This post is simply putting few facts together and my own interpretation of what it means in the Squeeze to come. This is not a financial advice, just the opinion of a humble Ape with couple of wrinkles.
Mods, please review and flag as appropriate. Apes, feel free to comment, correct or debate. At the end of the day this is my opinion, not better than any of yours.
In this post, I am going to cover what is happening to the VIX, what is happening with the 10 Year treasury note, its link to inflation, and why all this is the beginning of the end of the GME saga, and I believe the squeeze is getting closer (no dates provided if that is what you are after, sorry).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust no one. A shill tried to recruit me yesterday. </title>
      <link>/posts/nrpy23.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 22:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nrpy23.html</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a lot of comments from people wondering why shills are working for hedge funds, after reading the DD because it&amp;rsquo;s pretty clear they&amp;rsquo;re going to be out of a job very soon.
I actually put some thought into the situation after this exchange and I believe it&amp;rsquo;s a common misconception. The majority of shills out there on Reddit, Twitter, and YouTube aren&amp;rsquo;t Citadel interns or hired off of LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DD into fractional GME shares cost after transferring from Robinhood to another broker </title>
      <link>/posts/nglxti.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nglxti.html</guid>
      <description>I think that Robinhood has a big problem on their hands (no surprises there). Maybe I never understood PFOF until now, but here is a breakdown of how they were stealing my money and fudging the receipts when I bought fractional shares with them. I would highly recommend that anyone else who bought fractional shares of GME from Robinhood, and then transferred to another broker, check the reported costs.
On Jan 27, 2021 I opened a Robinhood account and spent $300 on fractional shares of GME right at market close and into after market hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Funds Might Lose Big on the Option Chain </title>
      <link>/posts/movs0h.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 18:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/movs0h.html</guid>
      <description>I honestly can&amp;rsquo;t believe the time and dedication I&amp;rsquo;ve put into GME. This DD is a representation of how much I care about my 2 shares.
The summary was going to be my morning report for tomorrow, but I&amp;rsquo;ve decided I&amp;rsquo;m going to write down the process I take when I think about aspects of the stock market. I hope someone finds this useful.
What is going on in the option chain?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The relevance behind the late-night weekend office work/scheming. </title>
      <link>/posts/mtq26h.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 01:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtq26h.html</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all seen the posts of various office buildings with their lights on at odd hours of the night these last 2 days. Now what is the significance of these you might ask? I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to share some of my thoughts in an effort to connect (more significant) dots for some more wrinkley-brained apes than me.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in the NYC Finance scene for well over a decade and can provide insights on how that scene (and buildings) generally operate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEC Legalese to Ape Speak - FINAL CHAPTER: How Gamestop is using its SEC 10-K Filings to fight back against targeted naked short selling (aka My Magnum Opus) </title>
      <link>/posts/nuksk8.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 19:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nuksk8.html</guid>
      <description>​
[Update: Thank you all for the kind words and comments. I&amp;rsquo;ve responded to some of you at the bottom of my post in order to keep the conversation going so that everyone can see it]
INTRODUCTION:
The Gamestop Saga is an ever-evolving story. We have all come such a long way from when we first got involved by buying our first stock, posting memes, and wondering what the heck is going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🔥GME SHORT% BETWEEN 110% - 1564% OF FREE FLOAT🔥 MY DD - The Pile </title>
      <link>/posts/mozzor.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 21:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mozzor.html</guid>
      <description>Greetings everyone,
I like to start off saying: This is not financial advice and everyone is open to punch holes in these numbers.
For smooth brain apes TL;DR is at the bottom.
I&amp;rsquo;ve heard a lot of people say: &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t trust my word, do your own DD&amp;rdquo;. So i did.
I looked at the values on shortvolumes.com (wb). And for a lot of consecutive days, the volume short was more than half the total volume of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS THEORY - The EVERYTHING Connection [Reposted] </title>
      <link>/posts/moswde.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 15:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/moswde.html</guid>
      <description>EDIT 1: THE MODS DID NOT TAKE DOWN THE POST. THIS WAS A RESULT OF ME ATTEMPTING TO INCLUDE THE STORY BELOW IN EDIT 4 FROM A BLACKLISTED SITE ARTICLE WHICH CAUSED THE AUTOMOD TO DELETE THE POST. I hoped that the removal of the link fixed the text but it didn&amp;rsquo;t, this is a Reddit issue, not a mod one. LAY OFF THE MOD NARRATIVE
EDIT 2: Thank you everyone for the feedback so far; I posted this here as a means to incite further conversation and thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urgent DD Update from Hank, FTD time! </title>
      <link>/posts/mvo75j.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvo75j.html</guid>
      <description>I am not a financial advisor, and this is not financial advice.
Only edit: some of you have been linking me to posts saying that my prediction was just a day early. At first, I didn&amp;rsquo;t think it could be true but now I think there might be some credence because we closed at .01% today and that has only happened 2 other times (went up big the next day). Nevertheless, lets sit back and watch what happens tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Findings from my analysis of 605 data: Huge short position opened in January. Expanded in February and March. Has not been closed. </title>
      <link>/posts/nc1h4o.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 05:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nc1h4o.html</guid>
      <description>TA;DR: I looked at the 605 data - Citadel’s short position is so huge it’s distorted the order flow. It’s so massive you can see it merely by looking at where the GME orders are being executed. It also shows they haven’t closed.
TL;DR: Opening a huge naked short position requires market maker shenanigans. Leaving it unclosed requires further market maker fucketry. Both of these should be reflected in the proportion of GME shares executed at various market centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kenny might be in a bit of a pickle right now... </title>
      <link>/posts/n0fwx2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 14:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n0fwx2.html</guid>
      <description>Citadel owns 1473668 shares of AMD as of February 16th 2021.
AMD posted their earnings results yesterday after close.
EPS 52 vs EPS 44 (estimated). Meaning that they did almost 20% above expectations! Yet, the stock price dropped hard and is still dropping.
Who has 798300 calls and 560100 puts on MVIS? Citadel.
What did MVIS do in the past couple of days? Pumped from 10$ to 31$ and then dumped to 21$ this morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUY/SELL RATIO IS 5:1 ON FIDELITY - APES BUYING THE DIPS!!! 🦍💎🙌🏻 </title>
      <link>/posts/mnzb6o.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 06:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mnzb6o.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEC is Expecting the Need for a Mass Emergency Transfer of Customer Accounts Soon </title>
      <link>/posts/mvybgf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 05:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvybgf.html</guid>
      <description>Hello Apes, this isn&amp;rsquo;t a macro-analysis of the GME situation. Instead, this is a micro-analysis of a specific change in NSCC-2021-004. The purpose of this post is to further support the DD by c-digs (wb) as well as DD by other apes regarding the next few weeks.
Obligatory disclaimer: this is not financial advice, I&amp;rsquo;m just a chimpanzee who learned how to use the internet. I&amp;rsquo;m also not a financial ape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someone is turding in the dark pools again! </title>
      <link>/posts/n95vzr.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 14:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n95vzr.html</guid>
      <description>Typical disclaimer: I am retrieving Finra ADF (OTC dark pool) data from Fidelity using Time &amp;amp; Sales and running it through some spaghetti code I threw together for analysis purposes. As always, if you notice any errors in my data please point them out as I am prone to making mistakes and I&amp;rsquo;m no wrinkle brain.
For additional information, and understanding how I am doing all this, please read my post from last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New SEC filing from IEX seeking to overhaul and improve fairness in executing trades for retail investors. </title>
      <link>/posts/mqtid5.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 15:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mqtid5.html</guid>
      <description>Unpublished and scheduled to be posted on the federal register tomorrow. This will close several loopholes that market makers and HF have over retail investors for all trades routed to IEX.
https://public-inspection.federalregister.gov/2021-07676.pdf (wb)
The purpose of the proposed rule change is to enhance the Exchange’s Retail Price Improvement Program for the benefit of retail investors. Specifically, the Exchange proposes to make the following four changes: (i) revise the definition of Retail order in IEX Rule 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The market collapse has already begun and has been in motion since early February. Check your penny stocks. </title>
      <link>/posts/munkug.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 10:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/munkug.html</guid>
      <description>It recently occurred to me that in WSB, it’s against the rules to post about penny stocks, so not a lot of you follow the price action.
I&amp;rsquo;m a day trader and my trading strategy focuses entirely on penny stocks that are owned by hedge funds known to manipulate the market. Most stocks I invest in are all complete garbage, but I look for pump and dumps, obvious manipulation patterns, and anticipate runners based on near-identical charts of multiple companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>***Holy Shit: You must read this! Actually important!! Our voting rights for upcoming GME Annual shareholder meeting. Broker confirmed, I wasn&#39;t going to have a vote at all!!! I knew my shares could be lent out but didn&#39;t realize I couldn&#39;t vote in the upcoming proxy. Switched to cash account!! </title>
      <link>/posts/mktkdj.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 20:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mktkdj.html</guid>
      <description>​
HOLY SHIT! Dear Apes,
I decided to do some homework today. I know some of this is not new information but I contacted my broker and started asking questions. This was the part I found shocking&amp;hellip;(I&amp;rsquo;m removing the reps name so not to get them in trouble) and that I had no idea that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t call back my shares or even have a vote in the proxies &amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GameStop Removed from the Russell Microcap, May be Added to the Russell 1000 </title>
      <link>/posts/ntwd1h.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 21:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ntwd1h.html</guid>
      <description>(Originally posted Friday, reposting for visibility)
What’s up
FTSE Russell’s website has been crashing for the past 5 hours but I was finally able to get it to load. Today, FTSE Russell announced preliminary changes to some of their indexes.
Why is this important? Well previously, GameStop was in the Russell 2000, 2500, and Microcap indexes. You can see how companies are organized into these indexes here (wb) page 21.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME Ownership Analysis 5/28- Hedgies R FuQ </title>
      <link>/posts/nneevk.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 03:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nneevk.html</guid>
      <description>Hello fellow Apes,
Obligatory Disclaimer: I am not a Financial Advisor, and this is not Financial Advice. Always do your own homework. That being said.. lets get started.
TL,DR: Hedies R FuQ. I used data from FTSE Russell&amp;rsquo;s own Database &amp;lsquo;Mergent Online&amp;rsquo; to calculate the current ownership numbers for GME&amp;hellip; and my TITS ARE JACKED.
I found some very interesting ownership numbers for GME today. I am using Mergent Online as my data source, which is produced by FTSE Russell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naked Shorting and Cede and Co, A repost of my old post from 2 months ago that was removed from Stocks </title>
      <link>/posts/mvmd4t.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 18:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvmd4t.html</guid>
      <description>Preface/Repost edit: Doubt everything, Do not trust this or any other post made by anyone as is without doing your own research. Do not think this is the whole picture, it&amp;rsquo;s not. I am not a financial advisor and I could just be insane.
Since I saw u/atobitt referencing Cede and Co in his current DD I wanted to just put this back out into the world as this post never took off in r/GME or r/wallstreetbets (a couple hundred upvotes) like it did in r/stocks (5k+ upvotes + all the awards which is basically all my accounts karma) and I feel like the info could be useful for people who want a bit more background on Atobitts post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THE COMPANY BEHIND THE SHILL RECRUITMENT ON REDDIT </title>
      <link>/posts/msgi43.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/msgi43.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial advice, obviously.
So I would like to start by saying that all of this is public information. I started from the company&amp;rsquo;s Linkedin address posted in the message being sent to the redditors:
https://www.linkedin.com/company/lifewatermedia/ (wb)
The founder of the company is named Ty Hoffer (Tyson Clay Hoffer):
https://www.linkedin.com/in/ty-hoffer-079365b/ (wb)\
https://www.corporationwiki.com/Texas/Houston/tyson-clay-hoffer/36784041.aspx (wb)
It seems that this is not Ty&amp;rsquo;s first rodeo, he was the President of a company called Winning Media LLC (there is no Linkedin page for this company, but I found the actual website):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T&#43;21 FTD cycle **May 25-26th.** If we can break through $200, expect a significant price jump Today or Tomorrow [ Crossposting for Visibility ] </title>
      <link>/posts/nksg03.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 15:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nksg03.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This once in a lifetime oppertunity that is GME.. and how shareholders will see 10mil 20mil 30mil a share </title>
      <link>/posts/ntettq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 05:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ntettq.html</guid>
      <description>Ok guys I&amp;rsquo;ve been investing for awhile, Im not the most wrinkle brain but I&amp;rsquo;ve got a few&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ve invested in long term value stock, dividend stocks, but my favorite type (before I YOLO&amp;rsquo;ed it all in Gamestop) was the sub-penny stocks&amp;hellip;
(Please hang in there while I explain the opposite of GME)
For all you smooth brain apes out there a sub-penny stock trades between .0001 and .0009 and you have the oppertunity to make alot of money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Danske Bank&#39;s CEO is stepping down after suspicion of breaking the law&#34; Did DB work at night this weekend? Yes. </title>
      <link>/posts/mtu1te.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 05:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtu1te.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOIA RESPONSE RECEIVED: Federal Proceedings and Whistleblower/s Likely CONFIRMED regarding SEC and Melvin Capital. </title>
      <link>/posts/nhcj2p.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 21:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nhcj2p.html</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s up Apes
TLDR at the bottom.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been sitting on my FOIA requests for about two months now, not wanting to make a post until I received an actual response. My request for a fee waiver was granted, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to spend any $$$ better suited for more crayons to shove between my gorilla molars, but my request for an expedited process was denied. Apparently the financial risks to hundreds of thousands of Ape wallets doesn&amp;rsquo;t constitute a national emergency, so I had to wait two more months before hearing anything back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>~95% SHORT VOLUME THE PAST 3 DAYS ON MILLIONS OF SHARES SUDDENLY FOR IXG (iShares Global Financials ETF), WHICH CONTAINS MANY OF THE WORLD&#39;S BIGGEST FINANCIAL EQUITIES!!! WHAT IS GOING ON?? </title>
      <link>/posts/mr1gho.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 22:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mr1gho.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet MFAM, Motley Fool&#39;s Asset Management. You may be SHOCKED to hear, but you will not find any negative articles on the Motley Fool website for any of their current stock holdings.... </title>
      <link>/posts/ms7wbs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 17:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ms7wbs.html</guid>
      <description>​
https://preview.redd.it/f873m85tikt61.png?width=1147&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=1ce4090e570736176663166840f876f8f7a31966
Apes, I would like you to meet Motley Fool Asset Management https://www.mfamfunds.com/index.html (wb), the sister company of the Motley Fool.
This company has several funds and ETFs on their site. So I took a look at the top holdings for each one then did a search on motley fool for their articles to see if they are upholding their mission to help readers obtain financial information and discuss ways to make investment and personal financial decisions (wb) are just a propaganda machine to boost the stock prices of their holdings (spoiler alert: It&amp;rsquo;s the propaganda one)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now that HOC 2 &amp; 3 are out, I have something you have to see, Just take a look and see the stats, and let your mind extrapolate. </title>
      <link>/posts/nm18xg.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nm18xg.html</guid>
      <description>https://preview.redd.it/bqhzxjzexl171.png?width=1515&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9f0b09c339dc59d0d9e61a63e1355022f77e7d9d
This is 114 months from 4/14/21 there are so many data points you can&amp;rsquo;t see it&amp;rsquo;s absurd
So a beautiful autist wrote some code and put the data on tableau, it&amp;rsquo;s the harvested FINRA FTD data for all tickers available.
Link: https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/gmeshortsqueeze/viz/SECFails-to-DeliverData/SECFails-to-DeliverData (wb)
This is worth playing around with. But, when you do, you will come to the conclusion that this has been going on a long time, and has been predatory and systematic in nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t forget what they did. A running list of FUD. </title>
      <link>/posts/mnjqpw.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mnjqpw.html</guid>
      <description>Apes have been through a lot these last few months. There is no end to hedge fuckery. (wb)
Below is a list of notable times they tried to FUD Apes out of their positions.
When it comes time to hold past 1K, 10K, 100K, 1M.
Remember this list.
Feel free to post additional examples and I will update.
Cointelpro Techniques for Dilution, Misdirection, and Control of an Internet Forum(wb)  &amp;ldquo;Remember these techniques are only effective if the forum participants DO NOT KNOW ABOUT THEM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theory: ALL THE PIECES, pt. 1 – The Anatomy of the Crime of Citadel </title>
      <link>/posts/mn0q9q.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 20:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mn0q9q.html</guid>
      <description>“Behind every great fortune there is a crime” – Balzac
This post is the collective narrative behind the plays on GME by large institutions. This will be a multi-part DD post gathered from excellent insights on this sub. As there have been no open confessions of these activities by the perpetrators (a la Bernie Madoff), or books that have yet been written, this will only exist as a theory with pieces of evidence to support where we can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlackRock and share recall for voting: We aim to vote at 100% of meetings... </title>
      <link>/posts/musig6.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 15:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/musig6.html</guid>
      <description>Straight from their website.
We aim to vote at 100% of meetings where our clients have given us authority to vote their shares, and therefore vote at approximately 16,000 shareholder meetings in approximately 85 markets each year. With regards to non-U.S. holdings, generally we estimate that we vote successfully at approximately 90% of meetings. Of the remaining, 8% are not voted due to shareblocking and 2% are not voted due to either the fund’s leverage, impediments such as ballots received post cut-off date or post meeting date, or other restrictions like in-person attendance or power of attorney being required in order to vote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gary Gensler, 47%, Antitrust, and Yet Another Reason Why Citadel is Likely Irrevocably Fucked </title>
      <link>/posts/n84gzo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n84gzo.html</guid>
      <description>47%, Gary Gensler, Antitrust, and Citadel Gary Gensler talked about a lot of stuff at the hearing earlier this week. The representatives generally focused on a lot of garbage, and they have justifiably taken a lot of shit from this community for their piss poor understanding of the things they are supposed to oversee. Lost in the gamification discussion was Gary Gensler talking about market concentration and Citadel how 47% of all retail order flow is routed through Citadel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Look Back at What Michael Burry Knew </title>
      <link>/posts/nsmbnk.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 03:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nsmbnk.html</guid>
      <description>APES. It has been a very good week. Don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone try to tell you otherwise. Barely a week ago we were fighting for $180, now we have rock solid support at $245-250. It is all spelled out in black and white (green and red?) on the month-long chart: we are winning this battle.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know about you but it has been quite a journey to get this far. Lots of twists and turns and emotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time To Call Bullshit </title>
      <link>/posts/n8r19o.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n8r19o.html</guid>
      <description>Edit: Grammar and thank you for the awards! Credit goes to all the apes who are helping to slide the pieces together and doing legwork. There is so much complexity to all this by fucking design and without the sheer number of people who are working tirelessly daily, none of this may have come to light and retail would keep getting bent over.
Borrowing from u/ForgottenBob, this should help for a summary or TL:DR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hank needs YOU part II: Hank the Data Shepherd </title>
      <link>/posts/nr2gbi.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 02:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nr2gbi.html</guid>
      <description>************ I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice ************
Intro bahhhhhhhhhhhhh bahhhhhhhhhhhh bahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh. Woah apes, did you hear that? Oh no&amp;hellip;. it&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;.. it&amp;rsquo;s our greatest weapon&amp;hellip;. the computer apes&amp;hellip;.. the geniuses&amp;hellip;. THEY&amp;rsquo;RE HERE&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.
Alright apes, this is gonna be a strange post. So as many of you know, I recently sent out a request for coders/big brain apes for a DD that I plan to make. I am not joking when I say that I have received well over 350 messages (a testament to how many extremely intelligent apes that are in this sub).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Banks Are Selling Government Bonds to the Hedgies - The Floor is 250 Million Part 1 </title>
      <link>/posts/mtp8y1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtp8y1.html</guid>
      <description>TL;DR
Investment companies are filing for amendments to combine the liability of holdings not registered with the SEC investment companies and they&amp;rsquo;re buying government bonds through Principal Funds and filing those, while changing the language in their contacts regarding using those funds to up their liability insurance and assumedly collateral, or at best stability.
A number of these bonds have a value in the trillions.
Okay here we go
I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the entire weekend pouring through SEC filings, and they tell a slow but compelling story that&amp;rsquo;s been unfolding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I would not like to be betting against this guy. Must watch for GME investors. We are in safe hands </title>
      <link>/posts/msszf4.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 15:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/msszf4.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/15/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. McDonalds Day! </title>
      <link>/posts/mrekg3.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 13:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mrekg3.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 165.5, 172, 174, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some accurate data, straight from eToro API calls. </title>
      <link>/posts/npmaym.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 05:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/npmaym.html</guid>
      <description>Hello all! Sorry to beat the drum about this but I feel like it should be summed up one last time as I&amp;rsquo;m a stickler for accurate data and I have confirmation on some of the numbers that have been floating around the sub yesterday with regards to eToro.
Short version (TL;DR): I have confirmed by combing through the eToro APIs that there are exactly 96,660 GME holders on the eToro platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Ryan Cohens tweet really meant... </title>
      <link>/posts/mv8r74.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mv8r74.html</guid>
      <description>Hes referring to Ted 2 In his tweet
https://twitter.com/ryancohen/status/1384616641087086596?s=21
In the US we never saw this ad but in Europe it was all over. How do I know? I live in Europe now.
I showed it to my gf and she said “ah I know that bear, that’s from T2”
I said what do you mean T2 and she said yea it’s from a movie called T2. So i asked her why she called it that and she said she never saw the movie but that it was advertised as T2 in this ad where he is shaking a martini and turns around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chicago Code - How a whole city wants to bankrupt GameStop </title>
      <link>/posts/nf6i4o.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 09:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nf6i4o.html</guid>
      <description>​
https://preview.redd.it/um6m402o0uz61.jpg?width=330&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=970a65a4880c617707c3d4545d2c39c277587992
Welcome to The Chicago Code: Shitadel, a shitty crime drama television series created by Ken Griffin that aired on Reddit on the 18th of May.
Not financial adv&amp;hellip;yada yada bing bong. I am not from the US, so try to sue me for anything. I&amp;rsquo;ll wear a tinfoil hat and defend myself. Just an FYI: I&amp;rsquo;ll refer to &amp;lsquo;shorting&amp;rsquo; when I am talking about a superior put position. Given the past of the stock and the option anomalies, as well as typical SHF behavior, it is highly likely that superior put positions indicate a short position to drive the price down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget hiding FTD&#39;s in ETF&#39;s. They are being hidden right under our noses using the Continuous Net Settlement System. </title>
      <link>/posts/mwx5nk.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 14:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mwx5nk.html</guid>
      <description>So I just finished watching The Wall Street Conspiracy and I decided I wanted to dig a bit deeper to understand how naked short selling works. I highly suggest you watch the documentary as I found it really helpful to understand how hedge funds attack companies to achieve the Bankruptcy Jackpot. Link https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kpyhnmd-ZbU&amp;amp;ab_channel=Alven1111 (wb)
While digging around I found this article from 2008 (I know it&amp;rsquo;s a bit out of date) and it blew me away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reposting this comment from u/Left-Anxiety-3580... thoughts?! 🤔🚀🚀🚀 </title>
      <link>/posts/mrv7h2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 03:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mrv7h2.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUGE FTD Cycle DD update from Hank </title>
      <link>/posts/n1wqlg.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 15:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n1wqlg.html</guid>
      <description>Not a financial advisor. Not financial advice
Greetings, Apes. Today I was contemplating whether to cut my hair into a mohawk or to get a bald fade. Obviously, those are very similar. Today, I decided to listen to Linkin Park&amp;rsquo;s smash hit, &amp;ldquo;WAP,&amp;rdquo; which always gets me going. I was definitely feeling a little high cuz I had just consumed THREE, yes THREE, fig newtons when I got a message from another primate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citadel, Susquehanna, and other affiliated groups purchased an outrageous amounts of Calls on an ETF that goes UP when $SPY goes DOWN. I have included data from IBorrowDesk I took 2 weeks ago, SPXS was being Short Sold into oblivion. Check January 11th today on Iborrowdesk. Data has been altered. </title>
      <link>/posts/mteo47.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 15:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mteo47.html</guid>
      <description>Hi Guys, FOREWORD: HODL GME LIKE YOUR LIFE DEPENDS ON IT. (if you want too, im not your advisor just a random idiot.) Heres the links to go look yourself:
https://www.holdingschannel.com/bystock/?symbol=spxs (wb)
​
https://iborrowdesk.com/report/SPXS (wb)
Heres a screenshot I took from about 3 weeks ago showing some friends:
​
​
I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna sit here and tinfoil hat, but c&amp;rsquo;mon they aren&amp;rsquo;t even TRYING to hide they&amp;rsquo;re Bullish on SPY shitting the bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citadel is busier right now than any peak at any time on any day. </title>
      <link>/posts/mu20xx.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 14:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mu20xx.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of a Short Squeeze and Why No Ape Will Be Left Holding The Bag </title>
      <link>/posts/mos6zf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 14:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mos6zf.html</guid>
      <description>Part 1 – Anatomy of a Short Squeeze
Pick the first thing you can think off – let’s say, bananas. Then think of any characteristic of that banana, lets say “size of bananas”. I can assure you that, if you plot into a graph the size of every banana in the world, you would get a Gauss (normal) Distribution for that characteristic.
“μ” (mu) is the middle point, which is the most common size for bananas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRAYON-BRAINED MANIFESTO: BANKS ARE UNLOADING THEIR DEBT ONTO OUR PARENTS&#39; RETIREMENT ACCOUNTS. Call your parents and ask them how much of their retirement savings is allocated to BONDS. </title>
      <link>/posts/mtxtib.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 10:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtxtib.html</guid>
      <description>Apes- first, this is not financial advice, I have been snorting crayons non-stop for 48 hours straight and am about to go full-on RICK JAMES, BITCH mode all over your couch. 🖍
Edit: The information in the following post has been officially verified by the moderators of WallStreetBets!! This is like getting an &amp;ldquo;AAA&amp;rdquo; credit rating on one&amp;rsquo;s DD, I am honored.
If you or your parents have their retirement accounts PASSIVELY MANAGED BY BIG BANKS OR INSTITUTIONS, as opposed to actively-manages funds or having independent financial advisors, PLEASE LISTEN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail EASILY Owns 100-300% of the Remaining Float </title>
      <link>/posts/mwskkv.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 10:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mwskkv.html</guid>
      <description>Alright apes and apettes. Like the rest of you, I am jacked to the TITS after seeing the recent Gamestop 14A filing (wb). I wanted to see what the remaining float was and if retail ownership really could be over 100%. So what&amp;rsquo;s the remaining float after insider and institutional ownership?
​
Outstanding Float
As per the 14A filing, there are 70,771,778 Gamestop shares outstanding. Institutional Ownership (minus Ryan Cohen&amp;rsquo;s LLC) comes out to 32,433,338 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probably the last DD you&#39;ll ever need to read... The OTC Conspiracy - Shining Some Light into the Dark Pool data </title>
      <link>/posts/myf505.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 19:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/myf505.html</guid>
      <description>I know that collectively, we are anti-conspiracy right now, but as a simple ape, I just liked the way it rhymed.
What I&amp;rsquo;m presenting is 100% based on the publicly available published FINRA OTC data. The way FINRA presents their data makes it really difficult to spot anomalies and trends, so I decided to compile it into an Excel spreadsheet. The trends are clear. The data is revealing. And the Hedgies have some serious wedgies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME&#39;s MACD is telling us the fuse is LIT 🔥 </title>
      <link>/posts/mm1yie.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 13:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mm1yie.html</guid>
      <description>First thing&amp;rsquo;s fist: I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the hell I&amp;rsquo;m doing. I&amp;rsquo;m just an ape throwing my own feces at the wall and calling it DD. I&amp;rsquo;m not saying that to be cheeky, I&amp;rsquo;m saying that because I&amp;rsquo;m probably wrong about a lot in this post and would appreciate being corrected. I ain&amp;rsquo;t no goddamn financial advisor. Ain&amp;rsquo;t no goddamn financial advice. I just think the goddamn stock is nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The March to Zero Liquidity Pt. 2: The Beat Goes On. Just Slower. </title>
      <link>/posts/n4con3.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 01:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n4con3.html</guid>
      <description>Tick tock. Tick tock.
Yesterday, we reviewed volume data on GME for every day since mid-January (wb) in part one (of an undetermined number of posts). In that post, the data showed a trend of declining volume since the first squeeze and made a case for the increasing risk of slippage and volatility.
Given the short hedge funds have made volume drier than the steak my wife&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s made tonight, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming important to look for other indicators of the trend in this story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I think I solved the Rubix Cube and... it is so much bigger than everyone thought. </title>
      <link>/posts/n7e18t.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 01:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n7e18t.html</guid>
      <description>This is it. Game ends. I win.
Let me preface: I have been trying to crack this code for 3 days now. And after the Bill Gates divorce, I got on the right track all because of his relationship with Buffet. But it was always just out of reach of the right ideas. Without further ado. Thank you to all the apes who kept asking questions, kept making me question it in the comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/16/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. The great exercise! </title>
      <link>/posts/ms31d1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 13:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ms31d1.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 158.5, 162.5, 165.5, 172, 174, 176.5, 179, 180.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 186, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Motley Fool&#39;s money trail to Citadel </title>
      <link>/posts/msmh9e.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 07:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/msmh9e.html</guid>
      <description>NOT. FINANCIAL. ADVICE.
(Re-posting this again. I previously posted it at an ungodly hour for most Apes, so was requested to share again.)
I have seen quite a few posts recently about The Motley Fool&amp;rsquo;s business model, and decided to look a little more under the hood. From what I can see, they may have quite a direct connection with Citadel, and potentially enjoy a symbiotic relationship with them (through an important middleman).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick update from Hank - FTD Cycle </title>
      <link>/posts/mzzb65.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 21:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mzzb65.html</guid>
      <description>************ Not a financial advisor. Not financial advice************
https://preview.redd.it/8yfbwi2zasv61.png?width=1170&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=1c8705410d909110c224cc0a9a7e2ed710f13859
Apety apety apes. What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between GME and my wife? GME doesn&amp;rsquo;t fuck the mailman. Though my wife is a legal midget, GME is still wayyyyyyyyyyy more shorted than she is. Alright, enough about me. As always, remember to see my previous posts about the FTD cycle theory or you will be more confused than I am when my wife ISNT cheating on me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WE&#39;RE CREATING OUR OWN FUD: A Plea for More Moderation </title>
      <link>/posts/mrhqll.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 16:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mrhqll.html</guid>
      <description>I keep seeing posts like this one (wb) saying that &amp;lsquo;they&amp;rsquo; used dates to bring us down back in March. Or posts talking about shills and FUD and heavier moderation for MOASS like this one (wb) or this one (wb).
The simple truth of the matter is that we have tons of misinformation and confirmation bias floating around and we&amp;rsquo;re just FUDding ourselves. The perfect example is the dividend nonsense which flew around the sub like a whirlwind before people finally found the good DD (wb).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Price Action Nearly Identical To Jan Squeeze 🚀 </title>
      <link>/posts/mv2bx9.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 22:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mv2bx9.html</guid>
      <description>Salutations once again my fellow apes. u/possibly6 back with some juicy confirmation bias solely using technical analysis.
As always, this aint no mothafuckin financial advice, hoe. The views expressed here are solely my approach to investing in this specific equity. I ape an am.
obligatory.
​
Let&amp;rsquo;s get right down to business. I have reason to believe the price action we are seeing is nearly identical to January right before we ran ago 500+.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIP Jordan belforts career and wallstreet!!!Extreme level of deep confirmation bias and Dd for my beautiful apes. Proof that gme is going to explode. 🚀 🚀 </title>
      <link>/posts/molsu2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 06:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/molsu2.html</guid>
      <description>Edit#6 if you can read this before commenting. This has fucking nothing to do with Jordan beyond proving his bullshit move on from gme dead wrong
Before I cover this topic I need to first mention two things number one not financial advice two one of the major plot points I use has been slightly covered but I plan to dive into different correlations between this plot point and how it actually ties to the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convertible Bonds </title>
      <link>/posts/mmz5yx.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 19:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mmz5yx.html</guid>
      <description>EDIT 3: THIS SHOULD BE TAKEN AS GOOD NEWS!!!
The initial concern was that GameStop sold a bunch of bonds that have the option to convert into shares of common stock.
​
This means an owner of GameStop&amp;rsquo;s bond can convert (under certain circumstances) into shares of GME to cover a large short position, without being traded on the market.
​
I have been informed by a few people that they do not have a currently have CONVERTIBLE BONDS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jerkin&#39; it With Gherkinit : Forward looking Technical Analysis for the week of 5/10/21-5/14/21 </title>
      <link>/posts/n8qlbh.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 23:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n8qlbh.html</guid>
      <description>Hello, fellow apes!
Gherkinit here with another look forward at upcoming technical events, market fuckery, and some spectrum colored crayons.
This week I want to go over upcoming technical indicators and take a look at some things I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed happening over this last week, such as, disappearing volume, lying little boys from Bulgaria, and the apparent effects of inflationary naked short selling.
As always later tonight I will post a consolidated Video DD of this on my YouTube (wb) for those of you that don&amp;rsquo;t have the time to read through this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enter Zen Mode. The theory of all price movements - how price spikes up AND price spikes down are artifical - and SI% might skyrocket. </title>
      <link>/posts/n9qv27.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 06:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n9qv27.html</guid>
      <description>​
Preface ==========  Not a financial advisor. I also have no financial experience or qualifications. Thought I&amp;rsquo;d make that clear per a commenter on my last post who wasn&amp;rsquo;t happy with me. ;)
Also apologies if some of this doesn&amp;rsquo;t read right. A bit buzzed typing it up lmao. I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to clarify anything in the comments.
Hello apes. You might remember my previous posts. But just in case, I&amp;rsquo;ll add them here once more because I&amp;rsquo;d like to expand on them a bit further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actual theory about the 49% loss </title>
      <link>/posts/mo0ods.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 08:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mo0ods.html</guid>
      <description>It just occurred to me&amp;hellip;
They&amp;rsquo;re not reporting 49% loss on the short position itself.
Because like they say you dont lose til you sell. And if they covered, they&amp;rsquo;d have lost a lot more. The number 49% makes no sense to me as a short position loss the more I think about it. Because it would bankrupt them. They&amp;rsquo;d be -1000% not -49%
This occurred to me battling shills. So thank you shills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATTENTION: Implicit Volatility on 800 C&#39;s set to expire TOMORROW is rising .02/.03 a second </title>
      <link>/posts/mrq5pq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 22:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mrq5pq.html</guid>
      <description>Edit 1: At the risk of exciting people for no reason, I certainly don&amp;rsquo;t want to set expectations and crash them like how it is happened so many times. Please, instead, see this as evidence that there is something very wrong about GME.
Edit 2: The title should be IMPLIED volatility. Sorry, folks. Was just trying to get this out fast.
Edit 3: Some folks are saying this is IV counteracting theta decay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin address activity appear to mirror GME price movements </title>
      <link>/posts/nkde38.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 01:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nkde38.html</guid>
      <description>I am but a simple primate with a brain not too dissimilar in structure to a pebble you might use to skip into the ruddy waters of a small creek you grew up next to.
What follows is highly likely to be nothing more than evidence of my early onset dementia and it is certainly not any kind of advice, but I felt compelled to share it in the event it is a useful puzzle piece to anyone whose has been wondering about a possible relationship between hedge funds and crypto holdings, the sort that have been circling the rumor mill lately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🕵️ Proxy Voting DD v2 - Why GameStop is publicly addressing the MOASS with confidence and what will happen to retail votes </title>
      <link>/posts/naw85p.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 18:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/naw85p.html</guid>
      <description>Hello, fellow apes! 🦍 First of all, this is not financial advice. Do not take anything I say here as the absolute truth. Make your own due diligence and take your own conclusions.
I stopped going into Reddit and watching the ticker a few days ago because my bias was already 100% confirmed, but yesterday I started to receive comments and awards in my old post: Proxy Voting DD, (wb) and it caught my attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why we, and our whales, are waiting for the DTC/OCC regulations to [potentially] initiate the squeeze, NOT the recall </title>
      <link>/posts/mpp2yr.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mpp2yr.html</guid>
      <description>Large whales like BlackRock have the obvious potential to initiate a squeeze, were they to recall their large number of loaned out shares, but one thing most of you are missing is until these regulations are locked in they wont &amp;ndash; regardless of the recall/voting. All of you should read these posts below, they very plainly, and brilliantly, lay out what exactly those regs are doing for our whales (and the markets health/safety in general) in great depth, but to give you a simplified version:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLACKROCK, VANGUARD, and FIDELITY are going to NUKE 🔥 Shitadel!!! </title>
      <link>/posts/mr5s1k.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mr5s1k.html</guid>
      <description>How Investing Giants Gave Away Voting Power Ahead of a Shareholder Fight!
Disclaimer: financial advise! Fuck is that shit, I’m drunk and you bored so listen to me rap.
TA:DR (too ape didn’t read) Blackrock, Vanguard and Fidelity has every incentive to send us to the fucking 🌙🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀 strap the fuck in
So i was curious about the dynamics of a share recall and to see why the big names maybe will or will not recall shares so i started digging and found some stuff</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THE ATOM BOMB: THIS IS THE ONLY WAY CITADEL AND OTHER HEDGIES CAN STOP THE SHORT SQUEEZE. </title>
      <link>/posts/mtpni2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtpni2.html</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the last few months reading all the DDs, ingesting all the information, trusting but VERIFYING everything I read.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been here since late last year and I&amp;rsquo;ve been following along extremely closely.
The only way the hedgies and Citadel can STOP the short squeeze is the following:
 They can&amp;rsquo;t. =============  I&amp;rsquo;ve come to the unfortunate conclusion that this is the only option. They simply cannot.
You will be out of a job soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today was the lowest volume trading day since January 12! The last two times GME had such low volumes (both of which also occurred on a Tuesday), we saw huge volume on the next day. What will we see tomorrow??? 🚀🚀🚀 </title>
      <link>/posts/mlltpu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mlltpu.html</guid>
      <description>Hi fellow apes 🦍🦍🦍and welcome to Superstonk!
With these volumes, It looks like everyone took a nap today! Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the historical volumes and any relations we can see with share price changes.
&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- BOILERPLATE:
I still know nothing, I can&amp;rsquo;t do math good. PLEASE don&amp;rsquo;t listen to me! Obligatory 🚀🚀🚀
TLDR: Today was the lowest volume trading day since Tuesday January 12 (when the price $19.95)! Historically we have seen huge volume trading days (and big price gains) on the Wednesday and guess what tomorrow is?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A DD into Steven A. Cohen, one of the main villains in the GME saga... </title>
      <link>/posts/nb0261.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 21:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nb0261.html</guid>
      <description>If you know the enemy and know yourself, you need not fear the result of a hundred battles. If you know yourself but not the enemy, for every victory gained you will also suffer a defeat. If you know neither the enemy nor yourself, you will succumb in every battle. -Sun Tzu
Know your enemy. -Zack de la Rocha
As someone who has been hodling for many months and paying daily visits (truthfully, multiple daily visits) to the various subs we Apes have called home along the way, I have noticed a shift in focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The naked shorting scam using ETFs: mass shifting of FTDs from GME to 20&#43; ETFs &amp; 27&#43; billion dollars still owed in remaining SI </title>
      <link>/posts/n1vgbb.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n1vgbb.html</guid>
      <description>UPDATE: New FTDs and SI are available for early april. All figures have been updated and some text where relevantIn my recent post The naked shorting scam in numbers (wb) I looked at options activity that could be used for mass naked short selling (Deep ITM calls and married put trades) and weird OTC trade data for GME in 2021. Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve taken another look at the ETF data to help complete the picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A BRIEF OVERVIEW OF RECENT FILINGS FROM THE DTC, NSCC, AND OCC FOR DIPSHITS WHO KNOW FUCKALL ABOUT SECURITIES LEGISLATION AND GET CONFUSED BY LETTERS AND NUMBERS </title>
      <link>/posts/msh5mt.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 01:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/msh5mt.html</guid>
      <description>EDIT: I have posted an updated, further-depth overview of all DTC filings here(wb), and will be posting NSCC and OCC filings this week. Someone mentioned in a comment that they got all of the recent SEC filings mixed up so I slapped this together really quick. Hopefully it helps.
Big ups to u/c-digs who wrote nearly everything linked. If one of my summaries is hella wrong please let me know and I will fix it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fourier Analysis: Power Spectral Density of GME price cycles </title>
      <link>/posts/njuunj.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 10:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/njuunj.html</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m trying a cross-post here, hope I&amp;rsquo;m doing this right, I made some slight improvements after some review on the DD sub.
So hi everybody, I&amp;rsquo;ve been lurking for a while, thought I might have something to contribute to the hive-mind. I&amp;rsquo;m submitting this late at night California time cause it took me a while, it turned out to be very long. Anyway, good morning Euro friends! Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to visit you all again someday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on me contacting SEC about the 44m FTDs; Proposal for a &#39;The Game Did Not Stop&#39; Project </title>
      <link>/posts/mkjaxs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 12:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mkjaxs.html</guid>
      <description>First of all, a note behind my thinking regarding sending my findings to the SEC and FINRA: Regarding: https://www.reddit.com/r/GME/comments/mihbr1/i_have_contacted_the_sec_regarding_my_findings_of/ (wb) if you missed it
There were many of these comments:
 &amp;lsquo;they&amp;rsquo;re not gonna do anything&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;they&amp;rsquo;re in bed with the hedgies&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;now they&amp;rsquo;re gonna halt trading and screw the squeeze&amp;rsquo;  and while some may be from shills (last one especially), the first two are not an unreasonable sentiment to have at this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A string of events are unfolding that cannot be stopped </title>
      <link>/posts/nei95i.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nei95i.html</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I&amp;rsquo;m a smooth brainer with a lot of time.
So the reason for this little DD is because of a certain find by u/PapaTheSmurf and his post
https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/nd39dl/srnysearca202054_need_some_wrinkles_asap/ (wb)
The finding in question is as follows and it clicked in a couple of missing pieces to a theory I have about our secret whale.
https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/nysearca/2021/34-91901.pdf (wb)
This rule appears to provide an exemption for companies that fall under “investment companies” in obtaining shareholder permission before issuing securities that relate to acquisition of stock or assets of another company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look at the WAKE! - revisiting GME OTC trades and why the float is much bigger than anyone expects </title>
      <link>/posts/n0lmln.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 18:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n0lmln.html</guid>
      <description>Hello SuperStonk,
I&amp;rsquo;m u/Doom_Douche , You may remember me from posts such as &amp;ldquo;Deep Dive into Dark Pool Trading - How they might accidentally be showing us the number of synthetic shares&amp;rdquo; (wb) or &amp;ldquo;My banner submission. Let&amp;rsquo;s get back to our roots! 🦍🤝💪&amp;rdquo; (wb)
I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the hell I&amp;rsquo;m doing and I would rather be making memes but you asked for it and you are gonna get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MORE PROOF of Market Manipulation and Why we see Intense Price Action at Market Open and Close! </title>
      <link>/posts/mng5v1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 12:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mng5v1.html</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into some more evidence of market manipulation as well as an explanation of why we see &amp;ldquo;intense&amp;rdquo; price action at market open and close!
It’s that time of the month! NYSE Order Type data (wb) has finally come through for March-21, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into it to see what&amp;rsquo;s changed in the month of March-21. Are Shitadel up to their usual shenanigans again? We&amp;rsquo;ll investigate this and more.
There are two things I want to go through before we get into the new order type data:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Catastrophic Correlation Between Union Bank, Morgan Stanley, and Archegos Capital. </title>
      <link>/posts/mvcgf2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 10:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvcgf2.html</guid>
      <description>So today we saw that Union Bank had confirmed to closing over 400 locations. This can be seen through the following post: https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/mv6k4z/union_bank_confirms_emergency_closing_of_over_400/ (wb)
The reason this is very fascinating to observe is because it reveals a much deeper image of their collapsing empire. How does it do that you ask? Well, if you look at the Parent company of Union Bank it turns out it is: MUFG Bank.
From wikipedia:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQUEEZE MOMENTUM INDICATOR JUST FLIPPED TO BULLISH </title>
      <link>/posts/mno62o.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 19:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mno62o.html</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER This is no financial advise! I am not an experienced monkey. I just do like the colors and the crayon stick figures. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m gonna grab me some and munch on them. I don&amp;rsquo;t want you to set your expectations because of that post. Even consider this to be wrong!
Please feel free to correct me and to leave some feedback!
​
TL:DR Another Chart Indicator flipped from bearish to bullish!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boa actively boarding up at 10pm... Chase not. Downtown Chicago. </title>
      <link>/posts/mv7kf1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 03:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mv7kf1.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
