<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on (DD)uplicate! A Decentralized home for all GME DD</title>
    <link>/posts.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on (DD)uplicate! A Decentralized home for all GME DD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 11:08:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>4/20 “Share Recall” Explained- Why it’s important that shares must be recorded-Is this the Catalyst?🚀🚀🚀 If you’re still on Margin, CONTACT YOUR BROKERS </title>
      <link>/posts/mmt5rq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 14:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mmt5rq.html</guid>
      <description>April 9 update: This piece has been heavily edited from its original presentation. I&amp;rsquo;ve had plenty of shit talk about this post. I get it. Some of y&amp;rsquo;all think I&amp;rsquo;m fucking r*tarded for even posting this. But NOT ALL APES HAVE BEEN HERE SINCE JANUARY. I&amp;rsquo;m just trying to help in my limited capacity. And it seems to have helped thousands of apes get their affairs in order before liftoff, so I stand by this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MOASS Preparation Guide </title>
      <link>/posts/mm5qle.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 16:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mm5qle.html</guid>
      <description>Please read though this and possibly sticky this because I think it is very important that we all have an understanding on the game plan 🚀
Pre-liftoff Preparation https://preview.redd.it/pyg5a96r4sr61.jpg?width=1280&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=97c4b8bfe4b63214cee3c8e5aaed8d5519d4db10
 Brokers preparation - i think everyone should take the time to understand the nuances and rules that the broker applies on trading. Some brokers may have some sneaky fine prints. So you should make sure that nothing can get in the way of you and your tendies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hank&#39;s Big Bang: Quant Apes Glitch the Simulation </title>
      <link>/posts/nu9qq9.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nu9qq9.html</guid>
      <description>************ I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice ************
Edit: Credit for the correlation tables to u/phalanxhydra
Edit 2: I am retarded. It&amp;rsquo;s u/Ivorypetal.
Introduction Apes, because of the sheer amount of information in this post and because I wanted to get it to you at the beginning of this week because of earnings and the meeting, this post will not have the usual funny intro and memes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walkin&#39; like a duck. Talkin&#39; like a duck </title>
      <link>/posts/ml48ov.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ml48ov.html</guid>
      <description>TL;DR - I have prepared a case which strongly indicates that Citadel Securities, along with it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;affiliates&amp;rdquo; are committing securities fraud. On March 26th 2021, FINRA released a new citation against Citadel Securities for nearly 2 years worth of securities violations. The only reason Citadel HASN&amp;rsquo;T been busted for fraud is because they hide behind the veil of &amp;lsquo;unintentional&amp;rsquo; behavior. However, this post illustrates how Citadel&amp;rsquo;s actions flag ALL 3 corners of the fraud triangle- pressure, motivation, and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Charting for 4/5/2021, predicting the day&#39;s price action in detail with Warden. The great migration edition. </title>
      <link>/posts/mkkj0p.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 13:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mkkj0p.html</guid>
      <description>This is not financial nor investment advice. These are ideas and opinions for information purposes only.
This post will read bottom to top. It&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to refresh the page and see edits at the top
Historical supports and resistances:
116.5, 125.5, 132.5, 141, 145, 147.5, 150, 152.5, 156.5, 162.5, 172, 176.5, 182, 183.5, 184.5, 187.5, 190.5, 192, 195, 196.5, 197.5, 200, 209, 211.5, 214.5, 218, 226, 230, 234, 243, 250, 253, 256.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Got What You Quant - 6/2/21 Trading Analysis and a Deeper Dive Into Today&#39;s Tape </title>
      <link>/posts/nqzo1o.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 23:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nqzo1o.html</guid>
      <description>HOLY MOLY! GME has highest close since 1/29! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen yesterday&amp;rsquo;s POST (wb), I recommend taking a look before getting into today&amp;rsquo;s action, because BIG THINGS ARE HAPPENING! Congrats to the 💎🖐🦍 that like movies, as without you, GME wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be on the brink of launch. Prepare yourself, it&amp;rsquo;s time for the tea. This is not financial advice, my 🧠 is smooth.
​
Up until 5/27, GME price movements were strongly correlated to AMC, making the year to date R^(2) value between the two 76%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve been scraping data used by hedge funds for over a year now to make it freely available to everyone. I think I might start doing regular data reports on $GME on here if there&#39;s interest, let me know if you have any feedback on the report below. </title>
      <link>/posts/mlevq3.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 15:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mlevq3.html</guid>
      <description>Hey guys pdwp90 here, founder of Quiver Quantitative (wb) for those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know me by Reddit tag.
This report is primarily comprised of &amp;ldquo;alternative data&amp;rdquo; which can be loosely thought of as data that comes from outside of traditional sources like earnings reports. The reason this type of data gets me so jacked is because it&amp;rsquo;s data that retail investors (you guys) often have an edge over Wall Street in interpreting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRICE ACTION IS SHOCKINGLY similar to NOT ONLY the 2/24-3/10 runup, but also to the JANUARY run from $20 - $480. T&#43;35 / T&#43;21 elaboration. </title>
      <link>/posts/nrud2r.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 02:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nrud2r.html</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll start with the usual: I am not a financial advisor. I do not provide financial advice! Everything following this is opinion/observation. Much of my knowledge of the markets has been acquired through reading countless hours of DD posted by others in this sub.
I&amp;rsquo;m not one to buy into the echoed phrases of this sub&amp;hellip; but I am in fact JaCKeD tO tHe TiTs!
OBLIGATORY - BuY &amp;amp; HoDl!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New OCC filing seeks to amend the process for liquidating positions for suspended options clearing members. (Citadel is an options clearing member) SR-OCC-2021-004 </title>
      <link>/posts/mkpgss.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 17:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mkpgss.html</guid>
      <description>Some people are getting a little confused. These &amp;ldquo;auctions&amp;rdquo; are not for GME stonk or any other stock for that matter. These are for open options contracts in other companies that have yet to expire and will need to be sold to cover short positions. The OCC handles all options transactions while the NSCC handles securities (stocks) transactions.
This rule is set to drop tomorrow (April 6, 2021) on the federal register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is SR-DTC-2021-005? THE UPDATE !! </title>
      <link>/posts/ngwhzu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 10:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ngwhzu.html</guid>
      <description>Hello Fellow Apes,
I am writing this post to let Apes know that I was able to follow-up through the SEC and the DTCC on SR-DTC-2021-005 and to the follow-up on work in my initial post here (wb), and providing you now with the status update I received.
I would also like to report that the SEC and the DTCC once again were very gracious and timely in their responses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shorts must cover </title>
      <link>/posts/mw1txe.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 10:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mw1txe.html</guid>
      <description>So, from one smoothbrain to another. Apparently that u/Atobitt (wb) thing with his GOD TIER DD &amp;ldquo;House of cards&amp;rdquo; made some folks very insecure. Fuck, even I was completely devastated yesterday when I read it. With huge efforts I got my first wrinkle after thinking this through. Since I am not a genius, but I still want to pollute the internet like any other moron with my uninformed, unasked opinion, here is what I came up with, in hopes of helping some of you to make the right decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hank returns from the dead and takes a dump </title>
      <link>/posts/nhs1wy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 13:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nhs1wy.html</guid>
      <description>*********** I am not a financial advisor, this is not financial advice ************
Good morning apes, I&amp;rsquo;m back.
Boy is it good to be back, apes. I&amp;rsquo;ve missed you all. I&amp;rsquo;ve been gone for a while but have not left the cause. I&amp;rsquo;ve been lurking in the shadows, jacking off to DD, and huffing WD40. When I was just a child (a boy in Bulgaria), my father said he was going to the store to get cigarettes&amp;hellip; I think he&amp;rsquo;s still there, must&amp;rsquo;ve been a long line for those Marlboros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LATEST Failure-To-Deliver data from ALL 72 ETFs CONTAINING GME! ETFs containing 99% of all FTDs! </title>
      <link>/posts/ms6mvf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 16:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ms6mvf.html</guid>
      <description>Hello, this morning u/rensole did a request in his synopsis to analyse all the Failure-To-Delivers contained in the ETFs. So I made a Python script where I get all the latest FTD data from the 72 ETFs including GME. I will from now on post the FTD data for you apes. I hope you guys enjoy it! 🦍🦍
EDIT: Thank you so much for all your kind words! Love you all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, those patterns y&#39;all keep posting are real! The similarity in meme stock price movement is statistically significant and differs significantly from a control group of boomer stocks (answer to u/HomeDepotHank69). </title>
      <link>/posts/ns8dhk.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 15:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ns8dhk.html</guid>
      <description>So, this post is in response to u/HomeDepotHank69 ‘s request for DD into correlation between stock price movements.
TL/DR:
 Two different scientific methods showing that there is similarity and correlation between certain meme stocks and that this increased since Jan. A machine learning method asked to put stonk data into clusters based on their patterns over the last half year put the meme stonks GME, AMC, KOSS, and others together regardless of which bit of price data you choose to look at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚨EUROPOOR! 👀 Here is CARL HAGBERG&#39;s advice on HOW TO EXERCISE YOUR RIGHTS TO VOTE! Please do NOT capitulate. Do NOT acquiesce! YOU, Europoor, have a RIGHT. YOU have a VOICE. Follow Carl&#39;s ADVICE and heed Carl&#39;s words: &#34;VOTES HAVE VALUE!&#34; 🙏 Profit to the People. Power to the Players. 💎✊ </title>
      <link>/posts/nc8d2u.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 13:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nc8d2u.html</guid>
      <description>Hi Stonk, I will be happy to respond to your request below;
​
 &amp;hellip; for our Euro ape friends, many are still hitting resistance from their brokers on voting - can you provide maybe 5 bullet point steps they can do to maximize their voice and rights? Something I can post that really drives home the concrete measures they can take?
 ​
First. I want to make clear to the Euro apes that Europe is way ahead of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME Token Info </title>
      <link>/posts/nl0lk1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 21:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nl0lk1.html</guid>
      <description>I thought I&amp;rsquo;d summarize some information about the juicy morsel of information that was just discovered. I will try to keep it to information rather than opinion.
As has been rapidly circulating online, https://nft.gamestop.com/ (wb) was discovered. This site is real and official. You cannot fake a subdomain.
It has a curious little thing of numbers and letters near the bottom
Those who aren&amp;rsquo;t in crypto might not know that this is a an ERC (etherium) address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GME Wargame: A New Theory of Everything (My Final DD) 💗🦍🐒🚀🚀🚀 </title>
      <link>/posts/mvov2f.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mvov2f.html</guid>
      <description>Nothing in my post should be assumed to accuse anyone of anything.
This is my theory of everything. My Charlie Day-DD. This is, I think, the blueprint for getting us through these last few agonizing days. Sorry, it&amp;rsquo;s walls of text, but I think you&amp;rsquo;ll enjoy reading it.
This will be the only meme.
This is in all likelihood my final statement on the matter until new information comes to light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where in the world is SR-DTC-2021-005. We were told over 1 month ago it was taken down for formatting and would be replaced in no more than 2 weeks. Let&#39;s talk about it. </title>
      <link>/posts/ncnz1l.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ncnz1l.html</guid>
      <description>Where in the world is Carmen San Diego SR-DTC-2021-005 otherwise known as &amp;ldquo;stop counting your shares twice&amp;rdquo; rule. We have passed record number of rules in the past month, and yet we have still not seen my (now second favorite to SR-ICC-2021-007 (wb)) rule come back in any form. It&amp;rsquo;s gone, vamos, does not exist on the internet. What the fucking fuck**?**
The contents cannot be found on the federal register: Federal register with search applied (wb)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Just a Pyramid Scheme Part 1: The Missing Cornerstone </title>
      <link>/posts/nexfv4.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 01:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nexfv4.html</guid>
      <description>Hey Everyone!
What a fucking few days hey? GME closes almost 15% up, streamers that are more interested in their weird tarot card readings than actual data, FUD that we can barely even spot anymore, and an IV increase that is being hidden by a hidden company none of us have even talked about. Wait&amp;hellip; what was that last part? Oh yeah haha, another fucking DTCC that we have all neglected or overlooked or just got buried somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[UPDATE] BlackRock is about to delete Shitadel out of existence. </title>
      <link>/posts/n2jdy6.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 14:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n2jdy6.html</guid>
      <description>Hello apes/retards,
I&amp;rsquo;d like to provide an update to my previous post (wb) which outlines the possibility that BlackRock is in the process of deleting Shitadel out of existence. As of this morning, FINRA has reported no major material changes to its list of major institutional shareholders. However, it maintains the position of BlackRock Fund Advisors at &amp;amp; around 14 million shares.
For the past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been periodically reviewing the SEC&amp;rsquo;s page on BlackRock&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary firm (wb) in the hopes that a 13G or 13F would pop up indicating of the change in ownership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merrill Lynch gave control of my retirement to a hedge fund and gave them complete authority </title>
      <link>/posts/mtftnu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 16:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mtftnu.html</guid>
      <description>This is likely a gallary/media post. Check perma/wb links. I&amp;rsquo;ll add support for this later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIP /u/leavemeanon - WHERE ARE THE SHARES (Part 3) Resurrected </title>
      <link>/posts/nt8t9n.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 23:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nt8t9n.html</guid>
      <description>[Part 1] (wb)
[Part 2] (wb)
​
Hi all,
There were a lot of apes in the daily discussion thread wondering why the DD by /u/leavemeanon (wb) was gone. Turns out they&amp;rsquo;ve deleted their account for some reason, along with their posts. I did a bit of digging and managed to recover their posts (shoutout to https://camas.github.io/reddit-search (wb)), which I&amp;rsquo;ll be shamelessly reposting as there seems to be some demand:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME Calls for 4/16. A little nudge and Hedgies R Fukd. </title>
      <link>/posts/mqz8mp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 20:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mqz8mp.html</guid>
      <description>Important - See edit 2 at bottom of my write up.
A lot of calls have been added this week on top of what was already the most stacked options week for GME by far. There are no other weeks on the board that are even close to this week. The closest, in July is barely half by volume.
I&amp;rsquo;ll give the quick rundown on calls for the smooth brained and new apes to make sure you understand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
